<transcript lastedited="11.21.08 08:11:54">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.1.1  - Introducing Frame Relay]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts corporate bandwidth requirements for communication between several sites. A comparison of how dedicated lines and Frame Relay can satisfy these requirements is provided.<br><br>Topology and Bandwidth Requirements:<br>The sites are Chicago Headquarters, Toronto, New York, Dallas, and Mexico City. <br>Bandwidth requirements are as follows:<br>Chicago to Toronto: Download = 48 kbps, Upload = 16 kbps.<br>Chicago to New York: Download = 256 kbps, Upload = 112 kbps.<br>Chicago to Dallas: Download = 48 kbps, Upload = 16 kbps.<br>Chicago to Mexico City: Download = 48 kbps, Upload = 16 kbps.<br>Dallas to New York: Download = 12 kbps, Upload = 4 kbps.<br><br>Dedicated Lines:<br>Connections to satisfy bandwidth requirements are made between the sites using leased lines. Each span site is connected through a switch at the local telephone company's central office (C O) through the local loop, and then across the entire network.<br><br>The Chicago and New York sites each use a dedicated T1 line (equivalent to 24 DS zero channels) to connect to a C O Class 5 switch. Other sites use ISDN connections (56 kbps) to connect to the local C O switch. Because the Dallas site connects with both New York and Chicago, it has two locally leased lines. The network provider Class 5 switches interconnect using one DS zero between the respective C O's, except for the four DS zeros connecting Chicago to New York.<br><br>Frame Relay:<br>The diagram is the same as for dedicated lines, except that the Class 5 C O switches have been replaced with Frame Relay switches. The Frame Relay network uses PVC's to provide a logical path through the network of Frame Relay switches. Compare this to the physical path used by a dedicated connection. In a network with Frame Relay access, a PVC uniquely defines the path between two endpoints. <br><br>The connection from the Toronto, Mexico City, and Dallas Frame Relay switches are 48 kbps PVC's. The Chicago Frame Relay switch is connected to the New York switch using a 256 kbps PVC link. <br><br>Cost:<br>A table is provided to compare the cost of 64 kbps ISDN and 56 kbps Frame Relay connections.<br><br>Cost Item: Local loop monthly charge.<br>64 kbps ISDN: 185 dollars.<br>56 kbps Frame Relay: 85 dollars.<br><br>Cost Item: ISP setup.<br>64 kbps ISDN: 380 dollars.<br>56 kbps Frame Relay: 750 dollars.<br><br>Cost Item: Equipment.<br>64 kbps ISDN: 700 dollars.<br>56 kbps Frame Relay: 1,600 dollars.<br><br>Cost Item: ISP monthly charge.<br>64 kbps ISDN: 195 dollars.<br>56 kbps Frame Relay: 195 dollars.<br><br>Cost Item: One-time charges.<br>64 kbps ISDN: 1,080 dollars.<br>56 kbps Frame Relay: 2,660 dollars.<br><br>Cost Item: Monthly charges.<br>64 kbps ISDN: 380 dollars.<br>56 kbps Frame Relay: 280 dollars.<br><br>Equipment:<br>ISDN router: 700 dollars.<br>Cisco Router: 1,600 dollars.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
