<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 19:11:31">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.3.1  - Vulnerable Router Services and Interfaces]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts a tabular listing of vulnerable router services. The columns in the table are Feature, Description, Default, and Recommendation.<br><br>Feature: Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP)<br>Description: Proprietary Layer 2 protocol between Cisco devices.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: CDP is almost never needed; disable it.<br><br>Feature: TCP small servers.<br>Description: Standard TCP network services: echo, chargen, and so on.<br>Default: >=11.3: disabled, 11.2: enabled.<br>Recommendation: This is a legacy feature; disable it explicitly.<br><br>Feature: UDP small servers<br>Description: Standard UDP network services: echo, discard, and so on.<br>Default: >=11.3: disabled, 11.2: enabled<br>Recommendation: This is a legacy feature; disable it explicitly.<br><br>Feature: Finger.<br>Description: UNIX user lookup service, allows remote listing of users.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: Unauthorized persons do not need to know this; disable it.<br><br>Feature: HTTP server.<br>Description: Some Cisco I O S devices offer a web-based configuration.<br>Default: Varies by device.<br>Recommendation: If not in use, explicitly disable; otherwise, restrict access.<br><br>Feature: BOOT P server.<br>Description: Service to allow other routers to boot from this one.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: This is rarely needed and may open a security hole; disable it.<br><br>Feature: Configuration auto-loading.<br>Description: Router attempts to load its configuration via TFTP.<br>Default: Disabled.<br>Recommendation: This is rarely used; disable it if it is not in use.<br><br>Feature: IP source routing.<br>Description: IP feature that allows packets to specify their own routes.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: This rarely used feature can be helpful in attacks; disable it.<br><br>Feature: Proxy ARP. <br>Description: Router acts as a proxy for Layer 2 address resolution.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: Disable this service unless the router is serving as a LAN bridge.<br><br>Feature: IP directed broadcast.<br>Description: Packets can identify a target LAN for broadcasts.<br>Default: >=11.3: enabled.<br>Recommendation: Directed broadcast can be used for attacks; disable it.<br><br>Feature: Classless routing behavior.<br>Description: Router forwards packets with no concrete route.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: Certain attacks can benefit from this; disable it, unless your network requires it. <br><br>Feature: IP unreachable notifications.<br>Description: Router explicitly notifies senders of incorrect IP addresses.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: Can aid network mapping; disabled on interfaces to untrusted networks.<br><br>Feature: IP mask reply.<br>Description: Router sends an IP address mask of the interface in response to an ICMP mask request.<br>Default: Disabled.<br>Recommendation: Can aid IP address mapping; explicitly disable on interfaces to untrusted networks. <br><br>Feature: IP redirects.<br>Description: Router sends an ICMP redirect message in response to certain routed IP packets.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: Can aid network mapping; disable on interfaces to untrusted networks. <br><br>Feature: NTP service.<br>Description: Router can act as a time server for other devices and hosts.<br>Default: Enabled (if NTP is configured).<br>Recommendation: If not in use, explicitly disable; otherwise, restrict access.<br><br>Feature: Simple Network Management Protocol.<br>Description: Routers can support SNMP remote query and configuration.<br>Default: Enabled.<br>Recommendation: If not in use, explicitly disable; otherwise, restrict access.<br><br>Feature: Domain Name Service<br>Description: Routers can perform DNS name resolution.<br>Default: Enabled<br>Recommendation: Set the DNS server address explicitly, or disable DNS.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
