<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 11:12:10">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.3.7 - IPSec Security Protocols]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts a simulation activity in which you configure a central site router and a VPN client to provide VPN access for a remote user. Read the scenario and match the proper values to the entries in the Linksys Web interface screen for each VPN device.<br><br>Note: You may wish to contact your instructor for assistance in performing this activity.<br><br>Scenario:<br>A small company has set up Internet connectivity using a Linksys WRVS 4400 N business class router at their central site. The company would like to provide remote access to select users from remote locations, but they are concerned that the Internet traffic would not be secure. To address this concern, it has been suggested that they implement a remote access VPN that would allow telecommuters to securely access the central site network. Using the Linksys Quick VPN client software, remote users would be able to connect and establish a remote access VPN connection that encrypts and decrypts data.<br><br>Referencing the topology description above, fill in the blanks in the Linksys router's Web configuration utility to configure the remote VPN settings and configure a user account. The user's name is BobV, and his password is cisco 1 2 3.<br><br>Next Bob will initiate a remote VPN connection to the central site router using the Linksys Quick VPN client software. Fill in the blanks in the VPN client configuration utility to configure the client side of the VPN. The profile name is Central Site. Reference the correct username, password, and IP address.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Central Site:<br>- A server is connected to the central site router on the 192.168.1.0/24 network.<br>- The central site router LAN interface IP address is 192.168.1.1.<br>- The central site router Internet VPN interface IP address is 209.165.200.225.<br><br>Remote User:<br>Remote user PC2 is connected to the Internet cloud VPN tunnel. <br><br>Required Configuration Entries for the Central Site Linksys router:<br>User Name: BLANK<br>Password: BLANK<br>Re-enter to Confirm: BLANK<br>Entry Choices for Linksys Central Site router: <br>192.168.1.0<br>Robert<br>209.165.200.255<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>BobV<br><br>Required Configuration Entries for the Remote VPN Client:<br>Profile Name: BLANK<br>User Name: BLANK<br>Password: BLANK<br>Server Address: BLANK<br><br>Entry Choices for the Remote VPN Client:<br>User<br>Central Site<br>192.168.1.0<br>209.165.200.255<br>BobV<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>192.168.1.1<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>Branch Site<br>Robert<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>cisco 1 2 3]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
