<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 19:11:32">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.5.7  - Recovering a Lost Router Password]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts the router password recovery procedure.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>PC1 is connected to switch S1, which is connected to router R1. A system administrator laptop is connected to R1 using a console connection. <br><br>The router password recovery procedure is as follows:<br><br>Prepare the Device:<br>Prepare R1 for password recovery by booting it up in ROM mon mode.<br><br>Step 1. Administrator sets console connections parameters.<br><br>Step 2. Record the configuration register value. <br>R1> show version<br>show command output omitted<br>Configuration register is 0x2102<br>R1><br><br>Step 3. Power the router off and then on.<br><br>Step 4. Press Break on the terminal keyboard within 60 seconds of power up to put the router in ROM mon.<br><br>Bypass Startup:<br>Enable router configuration, but bypass the existing startup configuration.<br><br>Step 5. Change the config register setting. <br>rommon1> confreg 0x2142<br><br>Step 6. Reboot. Ignore saved configuration.<br>rommon 2> reset <br><br>Step 7. Skip the initial setup procedure.<br><br>Step 8. Type enable to get to the Router # prompt.<br><br>Access NV RAM:<br>Make the startup configuration available for viewing.<br><br>Step 9. Copy the startup-configuration from NV RAM to the running-config in RAM. <br>Router#copy startup-config running-config<br><br>Step 10. View passwords by running the show running-config command. <br>Router#show running-config<br><br>Reset Passwords:<br><br>Step 11. Enter global configuration mode using the configure terminal command.<br><br>Step 12. Set a new secret password.<br>Router(config)#enable secret cisco<br><br>Step 13. Issue the no shutdown command on every operational interface on the router. <br><br>Step 14. Set the location of the configuration register.<br>R1(config)#config-register 0x2102<br><br>Step 15. Exit configuration mode by pressing Ctrl-Z or typing end. <br><br>Step 16. Commit the changes.<br>Router#copy running-config startup-config]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
