<transcript lastedited="01.08.09 18:01:25">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.1.9 - General Guidelines for Creating ACL's]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple activities.<br><br>Activity One:<br>In this activity, you select the appropriate word or phrase to fill in the BLANK  and complete the sentence. Not all words are used, and some words may be used more than once.<br><br>Sentences:<br>One. An Access Control List (ACL) is a router configuration script that controls whether a router will BLANK or BLANK packets based on criteria found in the packet header.<br><br>Two. ACL's are often used in BLANK routers that are positioned between your internal network and an external network.<br><br>Three. A router with three active interfaces and two network protocols (IP and IPX) can have as many as BLANK active ACL's.<br><br>Four. For inbound ACL's, incoming packets are processed BLANK they are routed to an outbound interface.<br><br>Five. For outbound ACL's, incoming packets are processed BLANK they are routed to an outbound interface.<br><br>Six. At the end of every access list is an implied BLANK all traffic criteria statement. Therefore, if a packet does not match any of your criteria statements, the packet will be BLANK.<br><br>Words:<br>A.twelve<br>B.six<br>C.while<br>D.permit<br>E.before<br>F.blocked<br>G.allowed<br>H.deny<br>I.firewall<br>J.after<br>K.three<br><br>Activity Two:<br>In this activity, you indicate whether the statement applies to standard or extended ACL's or both.<br><br>Statements:<br>Can filter traffic based on the source IP address.<br>Can filter traffic based on the destination IP address.<br>Can filter traffic based on the protocol type.<br>Uses numbers 1 to 99.<br>Uses numbers 100 to 199.<br>Uses numbers 1300 to1999.<br>Can use a name instead of a number.<br><br>Activity Three:<br>In this activity, you evaluate the network policies and diagram to determine the best placement for one standard ACL and one extended ACL.<br><br>Network Policies:<br>Policy 1: Use a standard ACL to stop the 192.168.10.0/24 network from accessing the Internet through the ISP.<br><br>Policy 2: Use an extended ACL to stop the 192.168.30.0/24 network from accessing the Web /TFTP server.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>There are three LAN's with switches S1, S2, and S3. PC1, PC2, and PC3 are interconnected by routers R1, R2, and R3.<br><br>- PC1 is connected to switch S1, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/0 interface. This is local network 192.168.10.0/24.<br>- PC2 is connected to switch S2, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/1 interface. This is local network 192.168.11.0/24.<br>- PC3 is connected to switch S3, which is connected to router R3 on its FA0/1 interface. This is local network 192.168.30.0/24.<br>- Router R1 S0/0/0 WAN interface is connected to router R2 S0/0/0.<br>- Router R3 S0/0/1 WAN interface is connected to router R2 S0/0/1.<br>- Router R2 S0/1/0 serial interface is connected to the ISP.<br>- Router R2 FA0/1 interface is connected to the Web/TFTP server.<br><br>Potential placement locations<br>Select only one location per ACL, standard ACL and extended ACL.<br>- Router R1 interface FA0/0<br>- Router R1 interface S0/0/0<br>- Router R2 interface FA0/1<br>- Router R2 interface S0/1/0<br>- Router R3 interface FA0/1<br>- Router R3 interface S0/0/1]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
