<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:13">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.4.3  - Troubleshooting Frame Relay Configuration]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts an activity in which you read the scenario and review the description of the topology diagram. You then enter the necessary commands to configure Frame Relay and static routing on the central router R2 in the topology.<br><br>Note: Contact you instructor for assistance in performing this activity.<br><br>Scenario:<br>A company is transitioning from ISDN BR I links to a Frame Relay solution for the benefits provided by having permanent connections. As the network administrator, it is your job to coordinate the Frame Relay portion of the transition. The network support specialist at each branch location has completed their configurations, and each is waiting for the completion of the central router configuration to test connectivity. All three locations are using Cisco 1841 series routers. Your tasks on the central router R2 are to:<br><br>One. Enable Frame Relay encapsulation on the S0/0/0 interface.<br>Two. Configure two subinterfaces with the specified IP address and DLCI under S0/0/0.<br>Three. Configure static routes to the LAN's at each branch site.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>The diagram shows a hub and spoke Frame Relay network with four routers: R1, R2, R3, and ISP. Router R2 is the hub, and routers R1 and R3 are spokes. Router R2 connects to the ISP router using a dedicated link.<br><br>Router Interface IP Addressing:<br>Router R1 S0/0/0.16 IP Address: 10.10.224.2 /30<br>Router R1 FA0/0 (local network) IP Address: 192.168.220.0 /24<br><br>Router R2 S0/0/0.635 IP Address: 10.10.224.1 /30<br>Router R2 S0/0/0.278 IP Address: 10.10.224.5 /30<br>Router R2 S0/0/1 IP Address: 209.165.200.225 /27<br><br>DLCI's and IP addresses to be assigned on central router R2:<br>R2 to R1 DLCI 635<br>R2 to R3 DLCI 278<br><br>Router R3 S0/0/0.16 IP Address: 10.10.224.6 /30<br>Router R3 FA0/0 (local network) IP Address: 192.168.147.0 /24<br><br>Router ISP S0/0/1 IP Address: 209.165.200.226 /27<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
