<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 13:12:32">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[8.2.5 - Gathering Symptoms]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts a flow chart describing the steps for gathering symptoms for network problems. Commands are also provided.<br><br>Steps for Gathering Symptoms: <br>Step 1. Analyze existing symptoms.<br>Step 2. Determine ownership. Is the problem within the autonomous system? If so, go to Step 3. Otherwise, contact the external administrator.<br>Step 3. Narrow the scope.<br>Step 4. Determine symptoms.<br>Step 5. Document symptoms. If the problem can be solved using the documented symptoms, solve the problem and document the solution. Otherwise, begin the isolating phase of the general troubleshooting process.<br><br>Commands:<br>Command: ping {host | i p-address}<br>Description: Sends an echo request packet to an address, then waits for a reply. The host | i p-address variable is the IP alias or IP address of the target system.<br><br>Command: trace route {destination}<br>Description: Identifies the path a packet takes through the networks. The destination variable is the hostname or IP address of the target system.<br><br>Command: telnet {host | i p-address}<br>Description: Connects to an IP address using the Telnet application.<br><br>Command: show i p interface brief<br>Description: Displays a summary of the status of all interfaces on a device.<br><br>Command: show i p route<br>Description: Displays the current state of the IP routing table.<br><br>Command: show running-config interface<br>Description: Displays contents of the currently running configuration file for a particular interface.<br><br>Command: [no] debug ?<br>Description: Displays a list of options for enabling or disabling debugging events on a device.<br><br>Command: show protocols<br>Description: Displays the configured protocols and shows the global and interface-specific status of any configured Layer 3 protocol.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
