<transcript lastedited="11.21.08 08:11:03">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.4.2  - Verifying Frame Relay Operation]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts the commands to verify Frame Relay operation, including interfaces, LMI, PCV status, and inverse ARP. Clearing Frame Relay maps is also covered.<br><br>Interfaces:<br>The terminal window shows the R1 output of the show interfaces serial 0/0/1 command. This command displays how the encapsulation is set up, along with useful Layer 1 and Layer 2 status information, including:<br>- LMI type.<br>- LMI DLCI. <br>- Frame Relay D T E /DCE type.<br><br>The R1 output of the show interfaces serial 0/0/1.102 displays the subinterface information, including the status and IP address.<br><br>Command output for R2 is also provided.<br><br>LMI:<br>The terminal window shows the R1 output of the show frame-relay lmi command. This command displays LMI type and statistics, including the number of status messages exchanged between the local router and the local Frame Relay switch. <br><br>Command output for R2 is also provided.<br><br>PCV Status:<br>The terminal window shows the R1 output of the show frame-relay pvc command. This command displays the status of all the PVC's configured on the router. You can also specify a particular PVC. <br><br>Command output for R2 is also provided.<br><br>Inverse ARP:<br>The terminal window shows the R1 output of the show frame-relay map command. This command displays the following information: <br>- 10.140.1.1 is the IP address of the remote router, dynamically learned via the inverse ARP process.<br>- 100 is the decimal value of the local DLCI number. <br>- 0 x 64 is the hex conversion of the DLCI number, 0 x 64 = 100 decimal. <br>- 0 x 1840 is the value as it would appear on the wire because of the way the DLCI bits are spread out in the address field of the Frame Relay frame. <br>- Broadcast / multicast is enabled on the PVC. <br>- PVC status is active.<br><br>Clearing Frame Relay maps:<br>The terminal window shows using the clear frame-relay inarp command on R1 to clear Frame Relay maps that are dynamically created using inverse ARP. The show frame-relay map command on both routers R1 and R2 confirm that the IP address for the remote router on this DLCI is no longer displayed.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
