<transcript lastedited="01.08.09 18:01:11">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.7.1 - Chapter Summary]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[This is a review and is not a quiz. Questions and answers are provided. <br>Question One. List the four types of reconnaissance attacks and provide an example of a tool that can be used for each type of attack.<br>Answer: <br>Internet information queries:<br>- n s lookup or whois<br>Ping sweeps:<br>- f ping or g ping<br>Port scans:<br>- N map or Superscan<br>Packet sniffers:<br>- Wireshark<br><br><br>Question Two. List the four types of access attacks.<br>Answer: <br>- Password Attack.<br>- Trust Exploitation Attack.<br>- Port Redirection Attack.<br>- Man-in-the-Middle Attack.<br><br>Question Three. List three types of D o S attacks and three types of D D o S attacks.<br>Answer: <br>D o S Attacks<br>- Ping of death attack<br>- SYN flood attack<br>- Packet fragmentation and reassembly attack<br>- E-mail bomb attack<br>- CPU hogging attack<br>- Malicious applet attack<br>D D o S Attacks<br>- SMURF attack<br>- Tribe Flood Network (T F N)<br>- Stacheldraht<br>- My Doom<br><br>Question Four. List and explain the anatomy of a worm attack and the four steps to mitigate the worm attack.<br>Answer: <br>The anatomy of a worm attack is as follows:<br>- The enabling vulnerability - A worm installs itself by exploiting known vulnerabilities in systems, such as naive end users who open unverified executable attachments on e-mails.<br>- Propagation mechanism - After gaining access to a host, a worm copies itself to that host and then selects new targets.<br>- Payload - After a host is infected with a worm, the attacker has access to the host, often as a privileged user. Attackers could use a local exploit to escalate their privilege level to administrator.<br><br>The following are the recommended steps for worm attack mitigation:<br>- Step 1 Containment - Contain the spread of the worm into your network and within your network. Compartmentalize uninfected parts of your network.<br>- Step 2 Inoculation - Start patching all systems and, if possible, scanning for vulnerable systems.<br>- Step 3 Quarantine - Track down each infected machine inside your network. Disconnect, remove, or block infected machines from the network.<br>- Step 4 Treatment - Clean and patch each infected system. Some worms may require complete core system reinstallations to clean the system.<br><br>Question Five<br>Refer to the description of the Tera Term connection screenshot and the R1 configuration output described below for R1 to answer the question.<br><br>Tera Term screenshot:<br>Host IP address: 192.168.10.1<br>Service selected: SSH<br>TCP port number: 23<br><br>R1 configuration:<br>hostname R1<br>username student secret cisco 1 2 3<br>line v t y 0 4<br>no transport input<br>transport input telnet<br><br>Question:<br>To increase administrative access security, you have applied the above configuration to R1. However, you are unable to establish an SSH connection to router R1. Assume that you were able to telnet to the router before, and that the hostname, i p domain name, and crypto key have been correctly configured. Which changes would correct this problem?<br><br>Answer: <br>On router R1:<br>- The transport input command should have been transport input ssh.<br>- The login local command is missing from the line v t y 0 4 configuration mode.<br>- The SSH port number in the Tera Term window should be referencing TCP port 22.<br><br>Question Six. List five vulnerable Cisco I O S network services and provide the best practices associated to them. For example, unused interfaces should be disabled.<br>Answer: <br>- Small services such as echo, discard, and chargen should be disabled.<br>- BOOT P should be disabled.<br>- Finger should be disabled.<br>- Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) should be disabled and secure HTTP S configured (if required).<br>- Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) v1 and v2 should be disabled and SNMP v3 configured.<br>- Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) should be disabled unless required.<br>- Remote configuration should be disabled.<br>- Source routing should be disabled.<br>- Classless routing should be disabled.<br>- no i p directed-broadcast should be configured to stop SMURF attacks.<br>- no i p proxy-arp should be configured to stop ad hoc routing attacks.<br><br>Question Seven. List the five required steps to enable the lockdown feature of SDM.<br>Answer:<br>Step 1. Select Configure.<br>Step 2. Select Security Audit.<br>Step 3. Click One-step lockdown.<br>Step 4. In the Cisco SDM warning dialog box, select Yes.<br>Step 5. Deliver commands to the router.<br><br>Question Eight. List the three steps required to update a router with a new Cisco I O S image file located on a TFTP server.<br>Answer: <br>Step 1. Ping the TFTP server to make sure that you have access to it.<br>Step 2. Use the show flash colon command to verify that the router has enough room in flash to accommodate the size of the Cisco I O S image file.<br>Step 3. Copy the new Cisco I O S image from the TFTP server using the copy tftp flash colon command in privileged EXEC mode.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
