<transcript lastedited="11.17.08 08:11:56">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[1.2.2  - WAN Physical Layer Concepts]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts WAN Physical Layer terminology and equipment found at a company (subscriber) and a WAN service provider.<br><br>Company (subscriber) equipment:<br>- Customer Premises Equipment (CPE) - The devices and inside wiring located at the premises of the subscriber and connected with a telecommunication channel of the carrier. <br>- Data Communications Equipment (DCE) - Also called data circuit-terminating equipment, the DCE consists of devices that put data on the local loop. In the diagram, the DCE is a modem.<br>- Data Terminal Equipment (D T E) - The customer devices that pass the data from a customer network or host computer for transmission over the WAN. The D T E connects to the local loop through the DCE. In the diagram, the D T E is a router.<br><br>WAN Service Provider equipment:<br>- Demarcation Point (Demarc) - A point established in a building or complex to separate customer equipment from service provider equipment. Physically, the demarcation point is the cabling junction box, located on the customer premises, that connects the CPE wiring to the local loop.<br>- Local Loop - The copper or fiber telephone cable that connects the CPE at the subscriber site to the C O of the service provider. <br>- Central Office (C O) - A local service provider facility or building where local telephone cables link to long-haul, all-digital, fiber-optic communications lines through a system of switches and other equipment. In the diagram, the C O is a building.<br>- C O Switch - A network device located in the C O that connects the service provider to the customer over the local loop.<br>- WAN Service Provider Network - Consists of high-speed data routers and switches. In the diagram, this is represented by a cloud filled with a router and several multilayer switches .<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
