<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 20:11:11">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.8.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.	Match the term to the associated description.<br>Terms:<br>A: Operating system weakness.<br>B: Unsecured user accounts.<br>C: Network equipment weaknesses.<br>D: Unsecured default settings.<br>E: Lack of consistency and continuity.<br>F: TCP/IP and ICMP weaknesses.<br>G: Lack of disaster recovery plan.<br><br>Descriptions:<br>One. Technological Weakness.<br>Two. Configuration Weakness.<br>Three. Security Policy Weakness.<br><br>2.	Which two pieces of information can be determined from opening the Cisco SDM homepage of a router? (Choose two.)<br>A.	Routing table.<br>B.	CDP neighbors.<br>C.	Snapshot of the router configuration.<br>D.	Interface status.<br>E.	Features supported by the Cisco I O S software.<br><br>3.	A technician has been asked to perform a Cisco SDM one-step lockdown test. Which location should be used to initiate the test?<br>A.	Diagnostic mode on the Firewall page.<br>B.	Configure mode on the Security Audit page.<br>C.	Test mode on the Security Audit page.<br>D.	Test mode on the Firewall page.<br><br>4.	Match the term to the associated description.<br>Terms:<br>A: Reconnaissance attack.<br>B: Password attack.<br>C: Port redirection.<br>D: Worm, virus, Trojan horse.<br>E: D o S attack.<br><br>Descriptions:<br>One. Dictionary cracking and brute force attack.<br>Two. Using a compromised host to pass traffic through a firewall that would otherwise be dropped.<br>Three. Using ping sweeps, port scans, and packet sniffers to gain information about a network.<br>Four. Flooding a network device with traffic in an attempt to render it unusable for legitimate traffic.<br>Five. Malicious software designed to damage a system, replicate itself, or deny services or access to networks, systems, or services.<br><br>5.	What is a major advantage of H I P S over H I D S?<br>A.	H I P S does not require host-based client software.<br>B.	H I P S consumes fewer system resources.<br>C.	H I P S can prevent intrusions.<br>D.	H I P S prevents the need to update signature files as often.<br><br>6.	What is the core or hub component of the Security Wheel?<br>A.	secure.<br>B.	monitor.<br>C.	improve. <br>D.	test.<br>E.	security policy.<br><br>7.	As part of a network security plan, where does Cisco recommend that administrators send events captured by syslog?<br>A.	flash.<br>B.	NV RAM.<br>C.	designated log hosts.<br>D.	designated TFTP clients.<br>E.	designated SNMP clients.<br><br>8.	Which protocol should be used when strong privacy and session integrity are needed for remote router administration?<br>A.	HTTP.<br>B.	SNMP.<br>C.	SSH.<br>D.	Telnet.<br>E.	TFTP.<br><br>9.	Match the policy to its description. Not all options are used.<br>Policies:<br>A: Account access request policy.<br>B: Remote access policy.<br>C: Risk assessment policy.<br>D: Audit policy.<br>E: Acceptable use policy.<br><br>Descriptions:<br>One. Defines the standards for connecting to the internal network from outside the organization.<br>Two. Specifies procedures to investigate incidents, ensure conformance to security policies, and monitor user and system activity.<br>Three: Defines how network resources may and may not be employed.<br>Four: Formalizes the process of how users request access to systems.<br><br>10.	Match the three items required to configure SDM to the steps in the proper sequence. Not all options are used.<br>Items:<br>A: Use the auto secure command to configure router security.<br>B: Enable the HTTP and HTTP S servers on the router.<br>C: Create a user account defined with privilege level 15.<br>D: Create a user account defined with privilege level 0.<br>E: Create an ACL to allow HTTP traffic into the router and apply it to the v t y's.<br>F: Configure SSH and Telnet for local login and privilege level 15.<br>G: Configure SSH and Telnet for local login and privilege level 0.<br><br>Step required to configure SDM:<br>One.<br>Two.<br>Three.<br><br>11.	Which three services should be disabled on a router to prevent security vulnerabilities? (Choose three.)<br>A.	Network Time Protocol (NTP).<br>B.	Domain Name System (DNS).<br>C.	Secure Socket Layer (SSL).<br>D.	Cisco Express Forwarding (C E F).<br>E.	Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP).<br>F.	Secure Shell (SSH).<br><br>12.	Which feature provides a straightforward one-touch device lockdown for configuring the security posture of routers?<br>A.	SSH.<br>B.	SDM.<br>C.	AutoSecure.<br>D.	SNMP.<br><br>13.	Match the description to the correct network management service.<br>Descriptions:<br>A: Application Layer protocol that provides a facility for retrieving and posting data for monitoring and management of devices in a network using TCP for 161.<br>B: Protocol designed to synchronize the time on a network of machines and runs over UDP using port 123.<br>C: Distributed database that maps hostnames to IP addresses using services on a designated server.<br><br>Services:<br>Network Time Protocol (NTP).<br>Domain Name System (DNS).<br>Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP).<br><br>14.	Which feature is a web-based-management tool for Cisco I O S software-based routers?<br>A.	SSH.<br>B.	SDM.<br>C.	AutoSecure.<br>D.	SNMP.<br><br>15.	Which three SDM wizards are available to configure a router? (Choose three.)<br>A.	security audit.<br>B.	firewall.<br>C.	DHCP.<br>D.	Q o S.<br>E.	routing.<br>F.	access list.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
