<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 19:11:45">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.1.2  - Common Security Threats]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts a list of network security vulnerabilities or weaknesses broken down by technology, configuration, and policy.<br><br>Technology:<br><br>TCP/IP protocol weakness<br>- Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP), File Transfer Protocol (FTP), and Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP) are inherently insecure.<br>- Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP), Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP), and Syn Floods are related to the inherently insecure structure upon which TCP was designed.<br><br>Operating system weakness<br>- Each operating system has security problems that must be addressed.<br>- UNIX, Linux, Mac OS, Mac OS X, Windows NT, 9x, 2K, XP, and Vista.<br>- They are documented in the Computer Emergency Response Team (CERT) archives at http://www.cert.org.<br><br>Network equipment weakness<br>- Various types of network equipment, such as routers, firewalls, and switches, have security weaknesses that must be recognized and protected against. Their weaknesses include password protection, lack of authentication, routing protocols, and firewall holes.<br><br>Configuration:<br>Weakness: Unsecured user accounts.<br>How the weakness is exploited: User account information may be transmitted insecurely across the network, exposing usernames and passwords to snoopers.<br><br>Weakness: System accounts with easily guessed passwords.<br>How the weakness is exploited: This common problem is the result of poorly selected and easily guessed user passwords.<br><br>Weakness: Misconfigured Internet services.<br>How the weakness is exploited: A common problem is to turn on JavaScript in Web browsers, enabling attacks by way of hostile JavaScript when accessing untrusted sites. I I S, FTP, and Terminal Services also pose problems.<br><br>Weakness: Unsecured default settings within products.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Many products have default settings that enable security holes.<br><br>Weakness: Misconfigured network equipment.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Misconfigured access lists, routing protocols, or SNMP community strings can open up large security holes.<br><br>Policy:<br>Weakness: Lack of written security policy.<br>How the weakness is exploited: An unwritten policy cannot be consistently applied or enforced.<br><br>Weakness: Politics.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Political battles and turf wars can make it difficult to implement a consistent security policy.<br><br>Weakness: Lack of authentication continuity.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Poorly chosen, easily cracked, or default passwords can allow unauthorized access to the network.<br><br>Weakness: Logical access controls not applied.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Inadequate monitoring and auditing allow attacks and unauthorized use to continue, wasting company resources. This could result in legal action against or termination of I T technicians, I T management, or even company leadership who allow these unsafe conditions to persist.<br><br>Weakness: Software and hardware installation and changes do not follow policy.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Unauthorized changes to the network topology or installation of unapproved applications create security holes.<br><br>Weakness: Disaster recovery plan is nonexistent.<br>How the weakness is exploited: Lack of a disaster recovery plan allows chaos, panic, and confusion to occur when someone attacks the enterprise.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
