<transcript lastedited="11.17.08 08:11:22">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[1.1.3  - The Evolving Network Model]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts the modules in the enterprise architecture. Six main areas are identified: the enterprise campus, enterprise edge, WAN and Internet, enterprise branch, enterprise data center, and enterprise teleworker. These are presented as a logical arrangement and as an example topology.<br><br>Enterprise Campus: <br>Connects users within the campus, the server farm, and the enterprise edge modules. The enterprise campus network is divided into four submodule areas: building access, building distribution, campus core, and data center, which consists of a server farm and network management.<br>- Building access submodule: Contains end-user workstations, IP phones, and Layer 2 access switches that connect devices to the building distribution submodule.<br><br>- Building distribution submodule: Provides aggregation of building access devices, often using Layer 3 switching. This submodule performs routing, quality control, and access control.<br><br>- Campus core submodule: Provides redundant and fast-converging connectivity between buildings, the server farm, and enterprise edge.<br><br>- Server farm and data center: Contains e-mail and corporate servers providing applications and file, print, e-mail, and Domain Name System (DNS) services to internal users.<br><br>Enterprise Edge:<br>Aggregates the connectivity from the various functional areas at the enterprise edge, and routes the traffic into the campus core submodule. The enterprise edge network is divided into four areas: e-commerce, Internet connectivity, WAN and metropolitan area network (MAN) site-to-site connectivity, and remote access including VPN.<br><br>WAN and Internet:<br>This is the service provider environment and is divided into three main areas: ISP services, Frame Relay, Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM), and MAN services, and the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN).<br><br>Enterprise Branch: Extends the applications and services found at the campus to remote locations.<br><br>Enterprise Data Center: Manages and maintains centralized data systems for the entire enterprise.<br><br>Enterprise Teleworker: Connects individual employees to network resources remotely, typically from their homes.<br><br><br>Example Topology:<br>The topology consists of four main areas: enterprise campus, enterprise branch, enterprise edge, and teleworker.<br><br>Enterprise Campus: <br>Building Access Layer devices are at the bottom of the hierarchy. The next level up is building distribution with four Layer 3 switches. Above that is the campus core with two Layer 3 switches that are connected to the Distribution Layer. <br><br>Branch office and teleworker areas interconnect to the enterprise campus through the enterprise edge devices (mainly routers) at the top of the diagram. The branch office connects to the enterprise campus via Frame Relay, and the teleworker connects via broadband.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
