<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 08:12:39">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.2.2 - Configuring a Standard ACL]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts standard ACL access-list command syntax. Parameters are listed along with a description of what they do. The process of removing an ACL and using the remark command are also covered.<br><br>Standard ACL Command Syntax:<br><br>The full syntax of the standard ACL command is as follows: <br><br>Router(config)#access-list access-list-number [deny | permit | remark] source [source-wildcard] [log]<br><br>Parameter: access-list-number<br>Description: Number of an ACL. This is a decimal number from 1 to 99, or 1300 to 1999 for a standard ACL.<br><br>Parameter: deny<br>Description: Denies access if the conditions are matched.<br><br>Parameter: permit<br>Description: Permits access if the conditions are matched.<br><br>Parameter: remark<br>Description: Adds a remark about entries in an IP access list to make the list easier to understand and scan.<br><br>Parameter: source<br>Description: Number of the network or host from which the packet is being sent. There are two ways to specify the source:<br>Use a 32-bit quantity in four-part, dotted-decimal format.<br>Use the keyword any as an abbreviation for a source and source-wildcard of 0.0.0.0 255.255.255.55.<br><br>Parameter: source-wildcard<br>Description: (Optional) Wildcard bits to be applied to the source. There are two ways to specify the source-wildcard:<br>Use a 32-bit quantity in four-part, dotted-decimal format. Place ones in the bit positions you want to ignore.<br>Use the keyword any as an abbreviation for a source and source-wildcard of 0.0.0.0 255.255.255.55.<br><br>Parameter: log<br>Description: (Optional) Causes an informational logging message about the packet that matches the entry to be sent to the console. The level of messages logged to the console is controlled by the logging console command.<br><br>The message includes the ACL number, whether the packet was permitted or denied, the source address, and the number of packets. The message is generated for the first packet that matches and then at five-minute intervals, including the number of packets permitted or denied in the prior five-minute interval.<br><br>Removing an ACL:<br>R1# show access-list<br>Standard IP access list 10<br>10 permit 192.168.10.0<br>R1#<br>R1#config t<br>Enter configuration commands, one per line. End with CNTL/Z.<br>R1(config)#no access-list 10<br>R1(config)#exit<br>R1#<br>*Oct 25 19:59:41.142: %SYS-5-CONFIG_I: Configured from console by console<br>R1#show access-list<br><br>R1#<br><br><br>Documenting an ACL using the remark command:<br>R1#config t<br>Enter configuration commands, one per line. End with CNTL/Z.<br>R1(config)#access-list 10 remark Permit hosts from the 192.168.10.0 LAN<br>R1(config)#access-list 10 permit 192.168.10.0<br>R1(config)#exit<br>R1#<br>*Oct 25 20:12:13.781: %SYS-5-CONFIG_I: Configured from console by console<br>R1#show run<br>Building configuration...<br><br>output omitted<br><br>Access-list 10 remark Permit hosts from the 192.168.10.0 LAN<br>Access-list 10 permit 192.168.10.0<br>!<br>output omitted]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
