<transcript lastedited="01.08.09 13:01:45">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[7.6.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.Which two statements are true about the DHCP server functions? (Choose two.)<br>A.When a client requests an IP address, the DHCP server searches the binding table for an entry that matches the MAC address for the client. If an entry exists, the corresponding IP address for that entry is returned to the client.<br>B.Clients can be assigned an IP address from a predefined DHCP pool for a finite lease period.<br>C.DHCP services must be installed on a dedicated network server to define the pool of IP addresses available to the clients.<br>D.The DHCP server can answer requests and assign IP addresses for a particular subnet only.<br>E.Each subnet in the network requires a dedicated DHCP server to assign IP addresses to the host on the subnet.<br>F.The DHCP server provides clients with an IP address, subnet mask, default gateway, and domain name.<br><br>2.Refer to the following command to answer the question. <br><br>Router(config)#i p dhcp pool 10.10.10.0<br><br>What does the string 10.10.10.0 used after the i p dhcp pool command specify?<br>A.Name of the DHCP pool.<br>B.Pool of IP addresses available for lease.<br>C.Range of excluded IP addresses.<br>D.IP subnet where the DHCP server resides.<br><br>3.Which three statements about DHCP are true? (Choose three.)<br>A.DHCP uses UDP.<br>B.The DHCP OFFER message is sent by the DHCP server after receiving a DHCP DISCOVER message from a client.<br>C.DHCP uses ports 67 and 68.<br>D.The DHCP REQUEST message is sent by a DHCP client to locate a DHCP server.<br>E.The DHCP ACK message is sent by the DHCP server to provide the DHCP client with the DHCP server MAC address for further communication.<br>F.All DHCP communications are broadcast.<br><br>4.Refer to the following topology description and partial show run output to answer the question.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Host A is connected to switch SW1, which is connected to router R1 interface FA0/0/0. Router R1 interface S0/0/0 is connected to router R2 interface S0/0/1, with IP address 10.10.1.254. <br><br>R1 show run output:<br>R1#show run<br><br>interface fast ethernet 0/0/0<br>i p helper address 10.10.1.254<br><br>output omitted<br><br>Router R2 is configured as a DHCP server. What would happen when host A sends a DHCP request to the DHCP server?<br>A.The request is dropped by router R1.<br>B.The request is forwarded to the DHCP server.<br>C.The request is forwarded to the DHCP server, but the DHCP server does not respond with an IP address.<br>D.Router R1 responds with an IP address.<br><br>5.Refer to the following command output to answer the question. <br><br>Router#:debug i p dhcp server events<br>DHCPD: DHCP DISCOVER received from client 0b07.1134.a029.<br>DHCPD: Assigned IP address 10.1.0.3 to client 0b07.1134.a029.<br>DHCPD: Sending DHCP OFFER to client 0b07.1134.a029 (10.1.0.4)<br>DHCPD: DHCP REQUEST received from client 0b07.1134.a029.<br>DHCPD: Sending DHCP NACK to client 0b07.1134.a029 (10.1.0.3).<br>output omitted<br><br>Router#show i p dhcp conflict<br>IP address: 10.1.0.3<br>Detection method: ping<br>Detection time: Jan 01 1999 00:00 AM<br><br>Based on the output, which statement is true regarding this DHCP exchange?<br>A.The client was successfully configured with the address 10.1.0.3.<br>B.The DHCP server offered the address 10.1.0.3 to the client.<br>C.The client requested 10.1.0.3 from the server.<br>D.The DHCP server could not ping 10.1.0.3.<br><br>6.Refer to the following command output to answer the question.<br><br>NAT1#show i p nat translations (output reformatted)<br>Pro: udp<br>Inside global: 198.18.24.211:123<br>Inside local: 192.168.254.7:123<br>Outside local: 192.2.182.4:123<br>Outside global: 192.2.182.4:123<br><br>Pro: tcp <br>Inside global: 198.18.24.211:4509<br>Inside local: 192.168.254.66:4509<br>Outside local: 192.0.2.184:80<br>Outside global: 192.0.2.184:80<br><br>Pro: tcp<br>Inside global: 198.18.24.211:4643<br>Inside local: 192.168.254.2:4643<br>Outside local: 192.0.2.71:5190<br>Outside global: 192.0.2.71:5190<br><br>Pro: tcp<br>Inside global: 198.18.24.211:4630<br>Inside local: 192.168.254.7:4630<br>Outside local: 192.0.2.71:5190<br>Outside global: 192.0.2.71:5190<br><br>Pro: udp<br>Inside global: 198.18.24.211:1026<br>Inside local: 192.168.254.9:1026<br>Outside local: 198.18.24.4:53<br>Outside global: 198.18.24.4:53<br><br>Based on the output, which statement is correct concerning the NAT configuration?<br>A.Static NAT is configured.<br>B.Dynamic NAT is configured.<br>C.PAT is configured.<br>D.NAT is incorrectly configured.<br><br>7.If an administrator chooses to avoid using NAT overload, what is the default timeout value for NAT translations?<br>A.1 hour<br>B.1 day<br>C.1 week<br>D.Indefinite<br><br>8.Match each characteristic to the corresponding NAT technique.<br>Characteristics:<br>A. Provides one-to-one fixed mappings of local and global addresses.<br>B. Assigns the translated addresses of IP hosts from a pool of public addresses.<br>C. Can map multiple addresses to a single address of the external interface.<br>D. Assigns the unique source port number of an inside global address on a session-by-session basis.<br>E. Allows external hosts to establish a session with an internal host.<br>F. Defines translations on a host-to-host basis.<br><br>NAT Techniques:<br>One. Dynamic NAT<br>Two. NAT with Overload<br>Three. Static NAT<br><br>9.Refer to the following command output to answer the question.<br><br>Router1(config)#i p nat inside source static 192.168.0.100 209.165.200.2<br>Router1(config)#interface serial0/0/0<br>Router1(config-i f)#i p nat inside<br>Router1(config-i f)#no shut<br>Router1(config-i f)#i p address 10.1.1.2 255.255.255.0<br>Router1(config)#interface serial 0/0/2<br>Router1(config-i f)#i p address 209.165.200.2 255.255.255.0<br>Router1(config-i f)#i p nat outside<br>Router1(config-i f)#no shut<br><br>Which host or hosts will have their addresses translated by NAT?<br>A.10.1.1.2<br>B.192.168.0.100<br>C.209.165.200.2<br>D.All hosts on the 10.1.1.0 network<br>E.All hosts on the 192.168.0.0 network<br><br>10.Refer to the following command output to answer the question.<br><br>R1(config)#i p nat pool nat-pool1 209.165.200.255. 209.165.200.240 netmask 255.255.255.0<br>R1(config)#i p nat inside source list 1 pool nat-pool1<br>R1(config)#interface serial 0/0/0<br>R1(config-i f)#i p address 10.1.1.2 255.255.0.0<br>R1(config-i f)#i p nat inside<br>R1(config)#interface serial s0/0/2<br>R1(config-i f)#i p address 209.165.200.1 255.255.255.0<br>R1(config-i f)#i p nat outside<br>R1(config)#access-list 1 permit 192.168.0.0 0.0.0.255<br><br>Which addresses will be translated by NAT?<br>A.10.1.1.2 to 10.1.1.255<br>B.192.168.0.0 to 192.168.0.255<br>C.209.165.200.240 to 209.165.200.255<br>D.Only host 10.1.1.2<br>E.Only host 209.165.200.255<br><br>11.Refer to the following topology description to answer the question.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Web Server 1 and several hosts are connected to Switch1, which is connected to the Router1 Ethernet interface. Router1 is connected to the Internet. <br><br>Web Server 1 is assigned a single IP address of 192.168.14.5/24. For hosts from the Internet to access Web Server 1, which type of NAT configuration is required on Router1?<br><br>A.Static NAT<br>B.Dynamic NAT<br>C.NAT overload<br>D.Port forwarding<br><br>12.Which NAT solution allows external users to access an internal FTP server on a private network?<br>A.Dynamic NAT<br>B.NAT with overload<br>C.Port forwarding<br>D.Static NAT<br><br>13.Refer to the following command output to answer the question.<br>Given the debug output from a Cisco router, what kind of address is 24.74.237.203?<br><br>s=10.10.10.3 to 24.74.237.203, d=64.102.252.3 [29854]<br>s=10.10.10.3 to 24.74.237.203, d=64.102.252.3 [29855]<br>s=10.10.10.3 to 24.74.237.203, d=64.102.252.3 [29856]<br>s=64.102.252.3 d=24.74.237.203 to 10.10.10.3 [9935]<br>s=64.102.252.3 d=24.74.237.203 to 10.10.10.3 [9937]<br>s=10.10.10.3 to 24.74.237.203, d=64.102.252.3 [29857]<br>s=64.102.252.3 d=24.74.237.203 to10.10.10.3 [9969]<br>s=64.102.252.3 d=24.74.237.203 to10.10.10.3 [9972]<br>s=10.10.10.3 to 24.74.237.203, d=64.102.252.3 [29858]<br><br><br>A.Inside local<br>B.Inside global<br>C.Outside local<br>D.Outside global<br><br>14.Which two statements accurately describe the RIP n g routing protocol? (Choose two.)<br>A.RIP n g has a limit of 15 hops.<br>B.RIP n g is a link-state routing protocol.<br>C.RIP n g uses UDP port 238 for updates.<br>D.RIP n g uses poison reverse.<br>E.RIP n g forwards IPv6 broadcasts.<br><br>15.Which two methods of assigning an IPv6 address to an interface are automatic and can be used in conjunction with each other? (Choose two.)<br>A.DHCPv6<br>B.Stateless auto-configuration<br>C.EUI-64<br>D.Static assignment<br>E.DNS<br><br>16.Match the IPv6 command to the appropriate description.<br>Commands:<br>A. i pv6 unicast-routing<br>B. i pv6 address<br>C. I p name-server<br>D. i pv6 host name<br>E. i pv6 router rip name<br><br>Descriptions:<br>One. Specifies the DNS server used by the router.<br>Two. Defines a static hostname-to-address mapping.<br>Three. Configure a global IPv6 address.<br>Four. Enables IPv6 traffic-forwarding between interfaces on the router.<br>Five. Enables RIP n g routing on the router and identifies the RIP process.<br><br>17.Refer to this IPv6 address:<br><br>2031:0000:0300:0000:0000:00C0:8000:130B<br><br>Which three items are equivalent representations of the full IPv6 address? (Choose three.) <br>A.2031:300::C0:8:130B<br>B.2031:0:300::C0:8000:130B<br>C.2031:1:0:3::C0:8000:130B<br>D.2031:0:0300:0:0:C0:8000:130B<br>E.2031::300:0:0:0C0:8000:130B<br>F.2031::0300::C0:8::130B]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
