<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:02">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[2.1.7  - Troubleshooting a Serial Interface]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple activities.<br><br>Activity One. In this activity, you identify whether the characteristic describes serial or parallel communications.<br><br>Characteristics:<br>- Used for most external communications.<br>- Used for short connections between interior components.<br>- Sends information across one wire, one data bit at a time.<br>- Sends over several wires simultaneously.<br>- Susceptible to clock skew and crosstalk.<br>- Cheaper to implement.<br>- Uses RS-232, V.35, and HSSI standards.<br><br>Activity Two. In this activity, you match the WAN component labels to the locations indicated in the diagram. Not all labels are used.<br><br>WAN Component Labels:<br>- DCE.<br>- D T E.<br>- Local Loop.<br>- Local Mile.<br>- Demarc.<br>- Last Mile.<br>- Last Loop.<br>- Demarcation.<br>- D E C.<br>- CPE.<br>- C O Switch.<br>- Service Provider.<br><br>Note: Contact you instructor on how to best perform this activity.<br><br>Activity Three. In this activity, you select the word or phrase to replace the BLANK in the sentences. Not all answers are used, and some sentences have more than one answer. <br><br>Sentence:<br>A. Time Division Multiplexing is a BLANK layer concept; it has no regard for the nature of the data that is sent out the channel.<br>B. Statistical Time Division Multiplexing uses a BLANK time slot length.<br>C. BLANK is an example of TDM.<br>D. The BLANK is the point in the network where the responsibility of the service provider ends.<br>E. The BLANK is equipment local to the customer and provides the BLANK side of a serial WAN connection.<br>F. BLANK is the default encapsulation type on point-to-point connections, dedicated link, and circuit-switched connections when the link uses two Cisco devices.<br>G. BLANK provides router-to-router and host-to-network connections over synchronous and asynchronous circuits.<br>H. BLANK is an industry standard, switched data-link layer protocol that handles multiple virtual circuits. It is a next generation protocol after BLANK.<br><br>Words: <br>- DCE.<br>- Variable.<br>- SONET.<br>- P P P.<br>- ATM.<br>- ISDN.<br>- HDLC.<br>- Frame Relay.<br>- Demarc.<br>- X.25.<br>- D T E.<br>- Dialup.<br>- CPE.<br>- SLIP.<br>- V.35.<br>- Physical.<br><br>Activity Four. In this activity, replace the BLANK with the command to accomplish the desired goal. <br>A. Which command verifies whether a cable is attached to serial 0/0/0 and whether it is D T E or DCE?<br>Command: Router #BLANK<br><br>B. Which command verifies the encapsulation type used on serial 0/0/0?<br>Command: Router #BLANK<br><br>Which command sets the encapsulation on a serial interface back to the Cisco default?<br>Command: Router (config-i f)#BLANK]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
