<transcript lastedited="01.13.09 09:01:03">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.6.1 - Summary and Review]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[This is a review and is not a quiz. Questions and answers are provided. <br>Question One. Compare and contrast the following terms: DLCI, LMI, and inverse ARP. <br>Answer:<br>DLCI - Data Link Connection Identifier<br>- VC's are identified by DLCI's, and the DLCI values are assigned by the Frame Relay service provider.<br>- Frame Relay DLCI's have local significance and no significance beyond the single link.<br>- A DLCI identifies a VC to the equipment at an endpoint.<br>LMI - Local Management Interface<br>- LMI is a keepalive mechanism that provides status information about Frame Relay connections between the router (D T E) and the Frame Relay switch (DCE).<br>- Three types of LMI's are supported by Cisco routers: Cisco, ANSI, and q 933 a.<br>Inverse ARP<br>- Inverse Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) obtains Layer 3 addresses of other stations from Layer 2 addresses, such as the DLCI in Frame Relay networks (which is the reverse of what ARP does).<br>- It is primarily used in Frame Relay and ATM networks, where Layer 2 addresses of VC's are sometimes obtained from Layer 2 signaling, and the corresponding Layer 3 addresses must be available before these VC's can be used.<br><br>Question Two. <br>Refer to the topology description below and the current router configuration for R1. Which command on R1 is required to statically configure a Frame Relay connection to R2? Traffic between sites must also support OSPF.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>The diagram shows a Frame Relay network with four routers: R1, R2, Frame Relay Switch, and ISP. Routers R1 and R2 connect to Frame Relay Switch. Router R2 connects to the ISP router using a dedicated link, simulated by a loopback interface.<br><br>Router Interface IP Addressing:<br>Router R1 S0/0/1 IP Address: 10.1.1.1 /30 connects to Frame Relay Switch S0/0/0.<br>Router R2 S0/0/1 IP Address: 10.1.1.2 /30 connects to Frame Relay Switch S0/0/1.<br><br>Frame Relay DLCI's:<br>R1 to R2: DLCI 102<br>R2 to R1: DLCI 201<br><br>Current Router R1 configuration commands shown:<br>interface s 0/0/1<br>i p address 10.1.1.1 255 255.255.252<br>encapsulation frame-relay<br>bandwidth 64<br><br><br>Answer:<br>frame-relay map i p 10.1.1.2 102 broadcast<br><br><br>Question Three. <br>Compare and contrast the following terms: access rate, C I R, C B I R, and B E.<br><br>Answer:<br>Access rate (or port speed)<br>- The capacity of the local loop.<br>- This line is charged based on the port speed between the D T E to the DCE (customer to service provider).<br>C I R - Committed Information Rate<br>- The capacity through the local loop guaranteed by the provider.<br>- Customers normally choose a C I R lower than the access rate to allow them to take advantage of bursts.<br>C B I R - Committed Burst Information Rate<br>- Negotiated maximum that a frame is allowed to burst above the C I R.<br>- Frames are marked as discard eligible (D E).<br>- It cannot exceed the access rate of the link.<br>B E - Excess Burst<br>- Amount of data above the C B I R, up to the access rate that frames may use to burst with no guarantee.<br>- Frames are also marked as discard eligible (D E) and cannot exceed the access rate of the link.<br><br>Question Four. <br>Refer to the topology description below and the current router configuration for R1. Router R1 is unable to establish point-to-point Frame Relay connections with routers R2 and R3. On the basis of the information provided, which configuration changes on R1 would correct the problem?<br><br>Network Topology:<br>The diagram shows a full-mesh Frame Relay network with three routers: R1, R2, and R3. Each router connects to the 10.1.1.0 /24 network through the Frame Relay cloud using its Serial0/0/0 interface.<br><br>Router Subinterface IP Addressing:<br>Router R1 S0/0/0.102 IP Address: 10.1.1.1 /30<br>Router R1 S0/0/0.103 IP Address: 10.3.3.1 /30<br><br>Router R2 S0/0/0.201 IP Address: 10.1.1.2 /30<br>Router R2 S0/0/0.203 IP Address: 10.2.2.1 /30<br><br>Router R3 S0/0/0.301 IP Address: 10.3.3.2 /30<br>Router R3 S0/0/0.302 IP Address: 10.2.2.2 /30<br><br>Frame Relay DLCI's:<br>R1 to R2: DLCI 102<br>R1 to R3: DLCI 103<br>R2 to R1: DLCI 201<br>R2 to R3: DLCI 203<br>R3 to R1: DLCI 301<br>R3 to R2: DLCI 302<br><br>Current Router R1 configuration commands shown:<br>hostname R1<br>interface s0/0/1<br>  encapsulation frame-relay<br><br>interface s0/0/1.201 point-to-point<br>  i p address 10.1.1.1 255 255.255.0<br>  frame-relay interface-dlci 201<br><br>interface s0/0/1.301 point-to-point<br> i p address 10.3.3.1 255 255.255.0<br>  frame-relay interface-dlci 301<br><br>Answer:<br>On router R1:<br>- The main serial interface and subinterfaces should be Serial0/0/0, Serial0/0/0.102, and Serial0/0/0.103, respectively.<br>- The wrong subnet mask is applied to the subinterfaces. The subnet mask should be 255.255.255.252.<br>- The DLCI's in the frame-relay interface-dlci command should be 102 and 103, respectively.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
