<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:28">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[2.1.2  - Time Division Multiplexing (TDM)]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts TDM examples of ISDN and synchronous optical networking (SONET). Also shown are DS0 (digital signal level zero) units and the T-Carrier hierarchy.<br><br>ISDN:<br>The diagram shows ISDN Basic Rate Interface (BR I) with three channels consisting of two 64 kilobits per second B-channels (B1 and B2), and a 16 kilobits per second D-channel. The TDM has nine timeslots, which are bit-interleaved and repeated in the sequence B1, B2, B1, B2, B1, B2, B1, B2, and D.<br><br>Two users are shown connected to an ISDN network termination type one (NT1) device and sharing the ISDN circuit of 64 kilobits per second B-channels. The control channel is the D channel.<br><br>SONET:<br>The diagram shows an example of statistical TDM with SONET /SDH. In the diagram, optical traffic arrives at the SONET multiplexer from four places at 2.5 Gigabits per second and goes out as a single stream at 4 times 2.5 Gigabits per second, or 10 Gigabits per second. <br><br>DS0 Units:<br>The diagram presents a table of DS bit types with the data rate and number of equivalent DS0 voice slots.<br><br>Signal Bit: DS0.<br>Rate: 64 kilobits per second.<br>Voice Slots: 1 DS0.<br><br>Signal Bit: DS1.<br>Rate: 1.544 Megabits per second.<br>Voice Slots: 24 DS0's.<br><br>Signal Bit: DS2.<br>Rate: 6.312 Megabits per second.<br>Voice Slots: 96 DS0's.<br><br>Signal Bit: DS3.<br>Rate: 44.736 Megabits per second.<br>Voice Slots: 672 DS0's or 28 DS1's.<br><br>T-Carrier Hierarchy:<br>The diagram presents the relationship between T-Carrier hierarchy units of transmission. T-carrier refers to the bundling of DS0's. In the diagram:<br>T1 = 24 DS0's (1.544 Megabits per second).<br>T1 C = 48 DS0's or two T1's (3.152 Megabits per second).<br>T2 = Two T1 C's (6.312 Megabits per second).<br>T3 = Seven T2's (45 Megabits per second).<br>T4 = Six T3's (274 Megabits per second).<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
