<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 12:12:48">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[7.2.5 - Configuring Dynamic NAT]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts the steps and command syntax involved in configuring dynamic NAT. An example configuration is provided.<br><br>Commands:<br>Step 1.<br>Action: Define a pool of global addresses to be allocated as needed.<br>Command: Router(config)#i p nat pool name start-i p end-i p {netmask netmask | prefix-length prefix-length}<br>Notes: Enter the global command no i p nat pool name to remove the pool of global addresses.<br><br>Step 2.<br>Action: Define a standard access list permitting those addresses that are to be translated. <br>Command: Router(config)#access-list access-list-number permit source [source-wildcard]<br>Notes: Enter the global command no access-list access-list-number to remove the access list.<br><br>Step 3.<br>Action: Establish dynamic source translation, specifying the access list defined in the prior step. <br>Command: Router(config)#i p nat inside source list access-list-number pool name<br>Notes: Enter the global command no i p nat inside source to remove the dynamic source translation.<br><br>Step 4.<br>Action: Specify the inside interface<br>Command: Router(config)#interface type number<br>Notes: Enter the interface command. The C L I prompt changes from (config)# to (config-i f)#.<br><br>Step 5.<br>Action: Mark the interface as connected to the inside.<br>Command: Router(config-i f)#i p nat inside<br><br>Step 6.<br>Action: Specify the outside interface.<br>Command: Router(config)#interface type number<br><br>Step 7.<br>Action: Mark the interface as connected to the outside.<br>Command: Router(config-i f)#i p nat outside<br><br>Step 8.<br>Action: Exit interface configuration mode.<br>Command: Router(config-i f)#exit<br><br>Example:<br>The diagram shows two PC's connected to the inside network cloud, which is connected to router R2. Router R2 is connected to the Internet cloud.<br><br>Inside Network:<br>PC1 IP address: 192.168.10.10<br>PC2 IP address: 192.168.10.11<br>Router R2 S0/0/0 interface IP address: 10.1.1.2<br><br>Outside Network:<br>Router R2 S0/1/0 interface IP address: 209.165.200.225<br><br>Router Output Configuration Commands:<br>i p nat pool NAT-POOL1 209.165.200.226 209.165.200.240 netmask 255.255.255.224<br>Defines a pool of public IP addresses under the pool name NAT-POOL1.<br>access-list 1 permit 192.168.0.0 0.0.255.255<br>Defines which addresses are eligible to be translated.<br>i p nat inside source list 1 pool NAT-POOL1<br>Binds the NAT pool with ACL 1.<br>interface serial0/0/0<br>i p nat inside<br>Identifies interface serial0/0/0 as an inside NAT interface.<br>interface serial0/1/0<br>i p nat outside<br>Identifies interface serial0/1/0 as an outside NAT interface.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
