<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:55">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[1.6.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.Which three items are considered to be WAN devices? (Choose three.)<br>A.Bridges<br>B.Modems<br>C.Routers<br>D.Layer 2 switches<br>E.Communication servers<br>F.Repeaters<br><br>2.Which layer of the hierarchical network design model is often referred to as the backbone?<br>A.Access<br>B.Distribution<br>C.Network<br>D.Core<br>E.Workgroup<br>F.WAN<br><br>3.Match the description to the associated term.<br>Descriptions:<br>A. A switching technology where each switch must evaluate the address of the packet to determine where to send it.<br><br>B. A switching technology where a virtual circuit is only physically in existence while a packet is traveling through it.<br><br>C. A switching technology that establishes routes through the switches for particular end-to-end connections.<br><br>D. A switching technology that has a pre-established dedicated circuit (or channel) between nodes and terminals.<br><br>Terms:<br>Circuit Switching<br>Packet Switching<br>Connection-oriented Packet Switching<br>Connectionless Packet Switching<br><br>4.Match the description of the packet-switched technology to the associated term.<br>Descriptions:<br>A. Provides a high-bandwidth Layer 2 network capable of managing data, voice, and video all on the same infrastructure.<br><br>B. Built on a cell-based architecture in which the cell has a fixed length of 53 bytes.<br><br>C. Operates at the Data Link Layer, and the PVC is identified by a DLCI.<br><br>D. Operates at the network layer, and the SVC is identified by a channel number.<br><br>Terms:<br>X.25<br>Frame Relay<br>ATM<br>Metro Ethernet<br><br>5.Which device is commonly used as Data Terminal Equipment?<br>A.ISDN<br>B.Modem<br>C.Router<br>D.CSU/DSU<br><br>6.Which type of WAN connection should be chosen when a dedicated point-to-point WAN communications path from the customer premises through the provider network to a remote destination is required?<br>A.ISDN<br>B.Analog dialup<br>C.ATM<br>D.Frame Relay<br>E.Leased line<br><br>7.How are Frame Relay virtual circuits identified?<br>A.C I R<br>B.DLCI<br>C.VPI<br>D.MAC<br>E.SPID<br><br>8.What WAN technology is designed for delivering data, voice, and video simultaneously over a TDM infrastructure?<br>A.ATM<br>B.Cable<br>C.Frame Relay<br>D.ISDN<br><br>9.Which Cisco architecture enables enterprises to offer important network services, such as security, new communication services, and improved application performance to every office regardless of its size or proximity to headquarters?<br>A.Enterprise Campus Architecture<br>B.Enterprise Data Center Architecture<br>C.Enterprise Branch Architecture<br>D.Enterprise Teleworker Architecture<br><br>10.At which layer of the hierarchical design model do users connect to the network?<br>A.Application<br>B.Access<br>C.Distribution<br>D.Network<br>E.Core<br><br>11.ISDN PRI is composed of how many B channels in North America?<br>A.2<br>B.16<br>C.23<br>D.30<br>E.64<br><br>12.The ability to connect securely to a private network over a public network is provided by which WAN technology?<br>A.DSL<br>B.Frame Relay<br>C.ISDN<br>D.PSTN<br>E.VPN<br><br>13.Which hierarchical design model layer is responsible for containing network problems to the workgroups in which they occur?<br>A.Application<br>B.Access<br>C.Distribution<br>D.Network<br>E.Core<br><br>14.Which term describes the cabling that connects the customer site to the nearest exchange of the WAN service provider?<br>A.CPE<br>B.C O<br>C.Local loop<br>D.DCE<br>E.D T E<br><br>15.Which goal can be accomplished by the implementation of the Cisco Enterprise Teleworker Architecture?<br>A.It allows the enterprise to add large branch sites that span large geographic areas.<br>B.It allows the enterprise to deliver secure voice and data services to workers no matter where or when they work.<br>C.To reduce remote security threats, it forces users who are located at main sites to log on to the resources.<br>D.It satisfies telephony requirements for users who are located at medium to large enterprise sites.<br><br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
