<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 11:12:26">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.2.4 - Broadband Wireless]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts the types of broadband wireless access. These include single router, meshed municipal WiFi, WiMAX, and satellite.<br><br>Single Router: The diagram shows a typical home deployment using a single wireless router. This deployment uses the hub-and-spoke model. A wireless router is shown with three laptops around it, two of which are in range and are connected. In a normal situation, any PC within range is connected. But if the router fails, there is no connectivity for any device.<br><br>Meshed Municipal WiFi: Most municipal wireless networks use a mesh topology. A mesh or series of access points (radio transmitters) is shown in the diagram. Each access point (AP) can communicate with at least two other access points. The mesh blankets the area with radio signals. Signals travel from access point to access point through this cloud. Three of the AP's connect to a backhaul node that connects to the ISP and the Internet.<br><br>WiMAX:<br>WiMAX (Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access) is based on the IEEE 8 0 2 dot 16 family of standards. A WiMAX network consists of two main components:<br><br>Tower - Similar in concept to a cellular telephone tower. <br><br>Receiver - Similar in size and shape to a PCMCIA card, or can be built into a laptop or other wireless device.<br><br>The diagram shows a home LAN with a WiMAX receiver connected over a non-line-of-sight wireless link to a WiMAX tower. That tower connects to another WiMAX tower using a line-of-sight microwave link. The second tower connects to a WiMAX tower station that connects directly to the Internet.<br><br>Satellite:<br>The diagram shows two-way satellite, which sends data from remote sites via satellite to a hub that then sends the data to the Internet. A satellite service subscriber with a dish is linked to a satellite that is linked to a dish at the satellite service provider's ISP.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
