<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 08:12:23">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.2.4 - Applying Standard ACL's to Interfaces]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts standard ACL configuration procedures and topology examples where they are applied. <br><br>Syntax:<br>Step 1. Use the access-list global configuration command to create an entry in a standard IPv4 ACL.<br>R1(config)#access-list 1 permit 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255<br><br>Enter the global no access-list command to remove the entire ACL. The example statement matches any address that starts with 192.168.10.x. Use the remark option to add a description to your ACL.<br><br>Step 2. Use the interface configuration command to select an interface to which to apply the ACL.<br><br>R1(config)#interface FastEthernet 0/0<br><br>Step 3. Use the i p access-group interface configuration command to activate the existing ACL on an interface.<br><br>R1(config-i f)#i p access-group 1 out<br><br>To remove an IP ACL from an interface, enter the no i p access-group command on the interface. The above example activates the standard IPv4 ACL 1 on the interface as an outbound filter.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>There are two LAN's with switches S1 and S2. PC1 and PC2 are interconnected by router R1. The S1 LAN is 192.168.10.0/24, and the S2 LAN is 192.168.11.0/24.<br>- PC1 with IP address 192.168.10.10/24 is connected to switch S1, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/0 interface.<br>- PC2 with IP address 192.168.10.10/24 is connected to switch S2, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/1 interface.<br>- R1 interface S0/0/0 is connected to network 10.1.1.0/30.<br><br>Example 1:<br>This ACL permits a single network. It allows only traffic from source network 192.168.10.0 to be forwarded out on S0/0/0. Traffic from networks other than 192.168.10.0 is blocked.<br><br>R1(config)#access-list 1 permit 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255<br>R1(config)#interface s0/0/0<br>R1(config-i f)#i p access-group 1 out<br><br>Example 2:<br>This ACL permits a single network and denies a specific host.<br><br>R1(config)#no access-list 1<br>R1(config)#access-list 1 deny 192.168.10.10 0.0.0.0<br>R1(config)#access-list 1 permit 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255<br>R1(config)#interface S0/0/0<br>R1(config)#i p access-group 1 out<br><br>Example 3:<br>This ACL denies a specific subnet and blocks traffic from the host PC1. It also permits all other LAN traffic to exit from router R1.<br><br>R1(config)#no access-list 1<br>R1(config)#access-list 1 deny 192.168.10.10 0.0.0.0<br>R1(config)#access-list 1 permit 192.168.0.0 0.0.255.255<br>R1(config)#interface S0/0/0<br>R1(config)#i p access-group 1 out]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
