<transcript lastedited="12.05.08 07:12:59">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[8.7.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.Match the items to the appropriate diagram type.<br>Items:<br>Cable type<br>IP address and subnet<br>Connection type<br>Device ID<br>Operating system version<br>Device type and model<br>Routing protocols<br>Connector type<br><br>Diagrams:<br>Physical diagram<br>Logical diagram<br><br>2.What is one symptom of a Physical Layer problem?<br>A.High CPU utilization<br>B.Excessive broadcasts<br>C.Slow STP convergence<br>D.Routing loops<br><br>3.A network administrator has received the output "Serial0 is up, line protocol is down" from the show interface s0 command. At what layer is this problem most likely being caused?<br>A.Physical Layer<br>B.Data Link Layer<br>C.Network Layer<br>D.Transport Layer<br><br>4.Which statement is true concerning network models?<br>A.While similar to the O S I model in construction, the TCP/IP model has more layers.<br>B.The Network Access layer in the O S I model incorporates both Physical and Data Link layers in the TCP/IP model.<br>C.Both users and Application Layer processes interact with software applications that contain a communications component in the O S I model.<br>D.TCP/IP communications only relate to the TCP/IP model.<br><br>5.Which three protocols could be involved in Network Layer problems? (Choose three.)<br>A.DNS<br>B.EIGRP<br>C.IP<br>D.RIP<br>E.TCP<br>F.UDP<br><br>6.Match the Application Layer protocol with the port number it is commonly associated with.<br>Application Layer Protocols:<br>FTP<br>HTTP<br>POP3<br>SMTP<br>SNMP<br>Telnet<br><br>Port Numbers:<br>20 and 21<br>23<br>25<br>80<br>110<br>161<br><br>7.A technician has been asked to troubleshoot a simple network problem that seems to be caused by software. Which troubleshooting approach should be suggested?<br>A.Bottom-up<br>B.Top-down<br>C.Divide and conquer<br>D.Middle-out<br><br>8.Which three questions are appropriate to ask when gathering information from a user? (Choose three.)<br>A.What does work?<br>B.Who did you call after the problem appeared?<br>C.When was the problem first noticed?<br>D.When does the problem occur?<br>E.What is your password?<br>F.What did you do after the problem occurred?<br><br>9.Which network troubleshooting tool can be used to test the physical medium for defects, such as near-end crosstalk?<br>A.Cable analyzer<br>B.Cable tester<br>C.Digital multimeter<br>D.Baselining tool<br><br>10.Which three documents are needed to efficiently diagnose and correct network problems? (Choose three.)<br>A.Network management command reference<br>B.Network configuration tables<br>C.Network device installation guide<br>D.Network topology diagrams<br>E.End-system configuration tables<br>F.Service provider documentation<br><br>11.What are three steps for establishing a network baseline? (Choose three.)<br>A.Determine the type of network management traffic to be collected and evaluated.<br>B.Determine the types of data to be collected and evaluated.<br>C.Identify devices and ports to be monitored.<br>D.Identify the virtual interfaces, V LAN's, and virtual routing tables to be monitored.<br>E.Determine the number of baseline tests to establish a typical picture of the network.<br>F.Determine the duration for baseline testing to establish a typical picture of the network.<br><br>12.What is associated with the first step in correcting Application Layer problems?<br>A.Analyzing existing symptoms.<br>B.Making a backup of configurations.<br>C.Making the initial hardware or software changes.<br>D.Pinging the default gateway to verify Layer 1 to Layer 3 functionality.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
