<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 08:12:08">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.7.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.	Which two statements correctly describe Cisco access control lists? (Choose two.)<br>A.	Extended ACL's are created in interface configuration mode.<br>B.	Extended ACL's filter traffic based on source and destination IP, port number, and protocol.<br>C.	Standard IP ACL's are numbered 1 to 99, and extended IP ACL's are numbered 100 to 199.<br>D.	Standard ACL's permit or deny traffic to specific IP addresses.<br>E.	Standard ACL's do not permit the use of wildcard masks.<br><br>2.	Which statement is correct regarding applying an access list to an interface?<br>A.	Access lists are applied in global configuration mode.<br>B.	Named access lists are applied using the ip access-name command.<br>C.	Standard access lists should be applied to an interface as close as possible to the destination.<br>D.	The command for applying access list 101 inbound is ip access-list 101.<br><br>3.	Which statement is a guideline to be followed when designing access control lists?<br>A.	Since ACL tests are executed in order, they should be organized from the most general condition to the most specific.<br>B.	Since ACL tests are executed in order, they should be organized from the most specific condition to the most general.<br>C.	Since all statements in an ACL are evaluated before they are executed, an explicit deny any statement must be written for an ACL to function properly.<br>D.	Since all statements in an ACL are evaluated before they are executed, an explicit permit any statement must be written in order for an ACL to function properly.<br><br>4.	Which two solutions can be implemented with ACL's? (Choose two.)<br>A.	Segment the network to increase available bandwidth.<br>B.	Create a firewall on a router to filter inbound traffic from an external network.<br>C.	Control traffic entering or exiting different areas of a local network.<br>D.	Distribute DHCP traffic to allow easier network availability.<br>E.	Allow or deny traffic into the network based on the MAC address.<br><br>5.	Match the following commands used with ACL's to their descriptions:<br>Commands:<br>ANY<br>show running-config<br>show access-list<br>HOST<br>show i p interface<br><br>Descriptions:<br>Substitutes for the 0.0.0.0 mask.<br>Indicates whether any ACL's are set on an interface.<br>Displays the contents of all ACL's on the router.<br>Represents an IP address and mask pair of 0.0.0.0 255.255.255.255.<br>Reveals the ACL's and interface assignments on a router.<br><br>6.	Which IP address and wildcard mask will test for hosts from an entire subnet of network 192.168.12.0 using a 29-bit mask?<br>A.	192.168.12.56 0.0.0.15<br>B.	192.168.12.56 0.0.0.8<br>C.	192.168.12.56 0.0.0.31<br>D.	192.168.12.84 0.0.0.7<br>E.	192.168.12.84 0.0.0.3<br>F.	192.168.12.84 0.0.0.255<br><br>7.	What kind of access list is created with the command i p access-list standard fastaccess?<br>A.	Turbo ACL<br>B.	Reflexive ACL<br>C.	Named ACL<br>D.	Dynamic ACL<br><br>8.	Refer to the ACL 101 statements listed below to answer the question. This ACL already exists on the router. <br><br>ACL Statements:<br>Access-list 101 deny tcp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255  eq 8080<br>Access-list 101 deny tcp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255  eq 80<br>Access-list 101 deny icmp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255<br>Access-list 101 deny icmp any 192.168.2.0  0.0.0.255<br>Access-list 101 permit ip any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255<br>Access-list 101 permit ip any 192.168.2.0  0.0.0.255<br><br>Question:<br>The network administrator wants to insert the command access-list 101 deny tcp any 192.168.1.0 0.0.0.255 eq ftp as the third line in the ACL shown. The network administrator enters the command in global configuration mode on the router. What effect does this have?<br>A.	It inserts the line in the desired position in the ACL.<br>B.	It inserts the line as the first statement in the ACL.<br>C.	It inserts the line as the last statement in the ACL.<br>D.	It deletes the entire list and replaces it with the new line only.<br><br>9.	Refer to the topology description and ACL statements listed below to answer the question.<br><br>Topology Description:<br>There are two routers, Router1 and Router2.<br>Router1 is connected to Router2 with a WAN link using Router1's S0/0/0 interface.<br>Router1 has two LAN's, Networks 192.168.1.0/24 and 192.168.2.0/24 are connected to its Ethernet interfaces.<br>Router2 has one LAN. Network 192.168.3.0/24 is connected to its Ethernet interface.<br><br>ACL Statements:<br>Router1(config)#access-list 201 deny icmp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255 any<br>Router1(config)#access-list 201 deny icmp any 192.168.2.0  0.0.0.255 any<br>Router1(config)#access-list 201 permit any any<br><br>Router1(config)#access-list 101 deny tcp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255 eq 8080<br>Router1(config)#access-list 101 deny tcp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255 eq 80<br>Router1(config)#access-list 101 deny icmp any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255<br>Router1(config)#access-list 101 deny icmp any 192.168.2.0  0.0.0.255<br>Router1(config)#access-list 101 permit i p any 192.168.1.0  0.0.0.255<br>Router1(config)#access-list 101 permit i p any 192.168.2.0  0.0.0.255<br><br>Router1(config)#int s0/0/0<br>Router1(config-i f)#ip access-group 101 in<br>Router1(config-i f)#ip access-group 201 out<br><br>Question:<br>Which statement correctly describes how Router1 processes packets with the configuration shown?<br>A.	Traffic exiting interface s0/0/0 is filtered by both ACL 101 and ACL 201.<br>B.	If a packet entering interface s0/0/0 matches a condition in ACL 101, the router continues comparing the packet to the rest of the statements in ACL 101 to make sure that no other statements might also apply.<br>C.	Router1 compares packets entering interface s0/0/0 first to all the ACL 101 statements for the IP protocol and then to all the ACL 101 statements for the ICMP protocol.<br>D.	A packet entering interface s0/0/0 is compared to each statement in ACL 101 until one statement matches the packet. Then the router drops or forwards the packet without considering the remaining statements in ACL 101.<br><br>10.	An administrator wants to implement lock-and-key access to a host within the company network for specific users who are connecting from outside the company network. What type of ACL would best suit the situation?<br>A.	Dynamic<br>B.	Reflexive<br>C.	Extended<br>D.	Time-based<br><br>11.	What type of ACL should the network administrator implement to limit Internet traffic during peak hours of the day?<br>A.	Dynamic<br>B.	Policy-based<br>C.	Reflexive<br>D.	Time-based<br><br>12.	Which statement correctly describes a reflexive access list?<br>A.	An ACL that allows IP traffic for sessions originating from inside the network, while denying traffic for sessions originating from the outside.<br>B.	An ACL that controls traffic based on the time.<br>C.	An ACL that uses an extended list to block users from traversing a router until they are authenticated.<br>D.	An ACL that only identifies the source of traffic.<br><br>13.	Categorize the following descriptions with the appropriate ACL type.<br>Descriptions:<br>Only checks source address.<br>Access list numbers 100 to 199.<br>Checks protocol and port numbers.<br>Only permits or denies entire protocols based on the network address.<br>Access list numbers 1- to 99.<br>Checks source and destination addresses.<br><br>Categories:<br>Standard IP ACL<br>Extended IP ACL<br><br>14.	Assuming the following ACL is correctly applied to a router interface, which two statements describe traffic on the network? (Choose two.)<br>	<br>	access-list 199 deny tcp 178.15.0.0 0.0.255.255 any eq 23<br>		access-list 199 permit i p any any<br><br>A.	All FTP traffic from network 178.15.0.0 will be permitted.<br>B.	All Telnet traffic destined for network 178.15.0.0 will be denied.<br>C.	Telnet and FTP will be permitted from all hosts on network 178.15.0.0 to any destination.<br>D.	Telnet will not be permitted from any hosts on network 178.15.0.0 to any destination.<br>E.	Telnet will not be permitted to any host on network 178.15.0.0 from any destination.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
