<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 08:12:01">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.6.1 - Summary and Review]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[This is a review and is not a quiz. Questions and answers are provided. <br>Question One. List the three "P" rule associated with access control lists.<br>Answer: <br>One ACL per protocol<br>- To control traffic flow on an interface, an ACL must be defined for each protocol enabled on the interface.<br>One ACL per direction<br>- ACL's control traffic in one direction at a time on an interface. Two separate ACL's must be created to control inbound and outbound traffic.<br>One ACL per interface<br>- ACL's control traffic for an interface, for example, FastEthernet 0/0.<br><br><br>Question Two. List the two basic rules associated with the placement of standard and extended ACL's.<br>Answer: <br>Standard ACL's<br>- Because standard ACL's do not specify destination addresses, place them as close to the destination as possible.<br>Extended ACL's<br>- Locate extended ACL's as close as possible to the source of the traffic denied. This way, undesirable traffic is filtered without crossing the network infrastructure.<br><br>Question Three. Refer to the topology description below to answer the question. ACL 10 configured on R1 is designed to block the host at 192.168.10.10 access to the 192.168.11.0 network, but all other hosts on the 192.168.10.0 network should be permitted access. However, the ACL does not accomplish this. Which changes would correct this problem?<br><br>Network Topology:<br>There are two LAN's with switches S1 and S2. PC1 and PC2 are interconnected by router R1. The S1 LAN is 192.168.10.0/24, and the S2 LAN is 192.168.11.0/24.<br>- PC1 with IP address 192.168.10.10/24 is connected to switch S1, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/0 interface.<br>- PC2 with IP address 192.168.10.10/24 is connected to switch S2, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/1 interface.<br>- Switch S1 IP address is 192.168.10.2/24.<br>- Switch S2 IP address is 192.168.11.2/24.<br>- R1 interface S0/0/0 is connected to network 10.1.1.0/30.<br><br>Commands used:<br>R1(config)#access-list 10 deny host 192.168.10.2<br>R1(config)#interface FA0/1<br>R1(config-i f)#i p access-group 10 in<br><br>Answer: <br>On router R1<br>- The host address was incorrectly specified. It should have been specified as 192.168.10.10.<br>- Because of the implicit deny statement, the remainder of the subnet was not permitted through. The remainder of the subnet should have been permitted using the access-list 10 permit any command.<br>- ACL 10 should have been applied to be in an outbound direction on interface FA0/1.<br><br>Question Four. Refer to the topology description in question 3 to answer the question. The SURFING ACL should permit only hosts on the 192.168.10.0 network to have Web and secure Web access. The hosts on the 192.168.11.0 network should not be permitted any access. The BROWSING ACL should permit return access only to traffic that originated from the 192.168.10.0 network. However, the ACL's do not accomplish this. Which changes would correct this problem?<br><br>Commands used:<br>R1(config)#access-list extended SURFING<br>R1(config-e x t-n a c l)#permit tcp 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255 any e q 23<br>R1(config-e x t-n a c l)#permit tcp any 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255<br>R1(config-e x t-n a c l)#exit<br>R1(config)#access-list extended BROWSING<br>R1(config-e x t-n a c l)#permit tcp any 192.168.10.0.0.0.0.255 established<br>R1(config-e x t-n a c l)#exit<br>R1(config)#interface FA0/1<br>R1(config-i f)#i p access-group SURFING in<br>R1(config-i f)#i p access-group BROWSING out<br><br>Answer: <br>On router R1<br>- The first permit statement of the SURFING ACL is allowing Telnet access (23). It should permit Web access (80).<br>- The BROWSING ACL requires the established keyword at the end.<br>- The ACL's have been applied to the wrong interface. They should have been applied to the serial 0/0/0 interface.<br>- The directions of the SURFING and BROWSING ACL's should have been reversed.<br><br>Question Five. Describe the three types of complex ACL's and their functions.<br>Answer: <br>Dynamic (Lock and Key):<br>- ACL's use an extended ACL to block users from traversing a router until they use Telnet or SSH to connect to the router and are authenticated.<br>- After being authenticated, specific dynamic ACL entries are activated on the ACL applied to the interface.<br>- These entries remain active for a specific period and then expire.<br>- This enables a user to authenticate and access resources that normally would be denied. Dynamic ACL's can be combined with other types of ACL's, such as extended ACL's.<br>Reflexive:<br>- Reflexive ACL's automatically create temporary entries based on upper layer session information. <br>- The entries are automatically deleted when the session ends.<br>Time-based:<br>- Time-based ACL's are similar to extended ACL's in function, but allow for access control based on time.<br>- A time range defines specific times of the day and week in which the ACL's are implemented.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
