<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 07:12:19">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.1.3  - What Is an ACL?]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts ACL's in a network and an explanation of what an ACL is. Some characteristics and rules for applying ACL's on a router are provided.<br><br>What is an ACL?<br>Network Topology:<br>There are three LAN's with switches S1, S2, and S3. PC1, PC2, and PC3 are interconnected by routers R1, R2, and R3.<br>- PC1 is connected to switch S1, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/0 interface.<br>- PC2 is connected to switch S2, which is connected to router R1 on its FA0/1 interface.<br>- PC3 is connected to switch S3, which is connected to router R3 on its FA0/0 interface.<br>- Router R1 S0/0/0 WAN interface is connected to router R2 S0/0/0.<br>- Router R3 S0/0/0 WAN interface is connected to router R2 S0/0/1.<br>- Router R2 S0/0/2 serial interface is connected to the Internet cloud.<br>- Router R3 S0/0/1 serial interface is connected to the HR subnet 172.17.0.0/20.<br><br>An ACL applied to R1 FA0/0 states: No video to S1, and no access to S2 for S1.<br>An ACL applied to R3 FA0/0 states: No updates, no FTP, and no Web.<br>An ACL applied to R3 S0/0/0 states: HR access.<br>An ACL applied to R2 S0/0/2 states: Allow e-mail and deny Telnet.<br><br>ACL's on a Router:<br>A router is shown, and an explanation of interfaces, protocols, and direction is presented. Protocols listed are IP, IPX, and AppleTalk, although IPX and AppleTalk are rarely used in today's enterprise networks. The diagram text states: With two interfaces and three protocols running, this router could have a total of 12 separate ACL's applied.<br><br>The three P's for using ACL's:<br>You can only have one ACL per protocol, per interface, and per direction.<br>One ACL per protocol (for example, IP or IPX).<br>One ACL per interface (for example, FastEthernet0/0).<br>One ACL per direction (for example, IN or OUT).<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
