<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 10:01:15">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.7.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.What is used to identify the path to the next Frame Relay switch in a Frame Relay network?<br>A.C I R.<br>B.DLCI.<br>C.FECN.<br>D.BECN.<br><br>2.Why are Frame Relay paths referred to as virtual?<br>A.There are no dedicated circuits to and from the Frame Relay carrier.<br>B.Frame Relay PVC's are created and discarded on demand.<br>C.The connections between PVC endpoints act like dialup circuits.<br>D.There are no dedicated circuits inside the Frame Relay carrier cloud.<br><br>3.Which statement accurately describes the split horizon problem with regard to a multipoint topology?<br>A.Split horizon must be disabled for all non-IP protocols.<br>B.Split horizon creates IP routing loops in multipoint domains.<br>C.Split horizon does not apply to broadcasts, so it does not protect protocols that use broadcast updates.<br>D.Split horizon prevents any point from accepting a valid update and forwarding to all the other points.<br><br>4.What are two reasons Frame Relay is more cost-effective than leased lines? (Choose two.)<br>A.Time division multiplexing.<br>B.Uses less equipment.<br>C.Optimized packet routing.<br>D.Shares bandwidth across a large customer base.<br>E.Dynamic IP addressing.<br><br>5.Match the status of a DLCI from the show frame-relay pvc command with its meaning.<br>Meaning:<br>The DLCI is programmed in the Fame Relay switch, but the other end of the PVC may be down.<br>The DLCI does not exist on the router.<br>The DLCI is programmed in the switch and is usable.<br>The DLCI does not exist on the Frame Relay switch for this router.<br>The DLCI is programmed on the other end of the PVC for the router.<br><br>Status:<br>Active.<br>Inactive.<br>Deleted.<br><br>6.What reliability advantage does Frame Relay offer over leased lines?<br>A.Frame Relay access circuits are higher grade circuits than leased lines.<br>B.The pathways for virtual circuits inside the carrier are meshed.<br>C.From end to end, a single virtual circuit uses a fixed error-checked path.<br>D.Frame Relay uses more sophisticated error detection methods.<br><br>7.Refer to the topology diagram description below to answer the question.<br><br>Topology Diagram:<br>The diagram depicts router Orlando and router DC connected through a Frame Relay cloud using their S0/0 interfaces. The Orlando interface S0/0 IP address is 192.168.1.25 /30. The DC interface S0/0 IP address is 192.168.1.26 /30. The Orlando connection to the cloud uses DLCI 100. The DC connection to the cloud uses DLCI 200.<br><br>What is placed in the address field of a frame that travels from the Orlando office to the DC office?<br><br>A.MAC address of the Orlando router.<br>B.MAC address of the DC router.<br>C.192.168.1.25.<br>D.192.168.1.26.<br>E.DLCI 100.<br>F.DLCI 200.<br><br>8.Which situation favors a multipoint topology over point-to-point?<br>A.When VLSM cannot be used to conserve addresses.<br>B.When using routing protocols other than IP.<br>C.When using a frame mesh topology to save access circuits.<br>D.When using a routing protocol that requires broadcast updates.<br><br>9.What is an advantage of configuring subinterfaces in a Frame Relay environment?<br>A.Makes the DLCI's globally significant.<br>B.Eliminates the need for using inverse ARP.<br>C.Reduces split horizon issues.<br>D.Improves flow control and bandwidth usage.<br><br>10.Which protocol can provide error correction for data that is transmitted over a Frame Relay link?<br>A.FECN.<br>B.FTP.<br>C.LMI.<br>D.TCP.<br>E.UDP.<br><br>11.Match the command to the description.<br><br>Command:<br>show interface<br>show frame-relay lmi<br>show frame-relay pvc<br>show frame-relay map<br>debug frame-relay lmi<br><br>Description:<br>View the status of virtual circuit and FECN /BECN statistics.<br>Verify that the router and Frame Relay switch are sending and receiving LMI packets properly.<br>Verify encapsulation, LMI type, LMI DLCI, and LMI status.<br>Verify LMI statistics.<br>Verify the IP address associated with a DLCI.<br><br>12.At which rate does a service provider guarantee to transfer data into the Frame Relay network?<br>A.baud rate.<br>B.timing rate.<br>C.data transfer rate.<br>D.committed information rate.<br><br>13.How are DLCI numbers assigned?<br>A.They are assigned by a DLCI server.<br>B.They are assigned arbitrarily by the user.<br>C.They are assigned by the service provider.<br>D.They are assigned based on the host IP address.<br><br>14.A router can reach multiple networks through a Frame Relay interface. How does the router know which DLCI to assign to the IP address of the destination network?<br>A.It consults the Frame Relay map.<br>B.It consults the routing table to find the DLCI.<br>C.It uses Frame Relay switching tables to map DLCI's to IP addresses.<br>D.It uses RARP to the find the IP address of the corresponding DLCI.<br><br>15.Match the term to the associated definition.<br>Terms: <br>C I R.<br>D E.<br>FECN.<br>BECN.<br><br>Definitions:<br>A bit that marks the frame to be dropped when congestion is present.<br>A bit set on every frame that a switch receives on a congested link.<br>Rate at which the service provider agrees to accept bits on the VC.<br>A bit set on every frame that a switch places on a congested link.<br><br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
