<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 12:12:31">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[7.1.4 - Configuring a DHCP Server]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts methods for verifying DHCP on the server and client.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Two LAN's, with network addresses 192.168.10.0/24 and 192.168.11.0/24, are connected by router R1. PC1 in LAN 1 is connected to switch S1, which is connected to R1 interface FA0/0. PC2 in LAN 2 is connected to switch S2, which is connected to R1 interface FA0/1.<br><br>PC1 IP address: 192.168.10.10/24<br>Switch S1 IP address: 192.168.10.2/24<br>Router R1 FA0/0 IP address: 192.168.10.1/24<br><br>PC2 IP address: 192.168.11.10/24<br>Switch S2 IP address: 192.168.11.2/24<br>Router R1 FA0/1 IP address: 192.168.11.1/24<br><br><br>DHCP-1 Button:<br>The show i p dhcp binding command displays a list of all IP address to MAC address bindings that have been provided by the DHCP service. The show i p dhcp server statistics command displays count information regarding the number of DHCP messages that have been sent and received. Because PC1 has not yet been powered up, no bindings or statistics are currently displayed in the output.<br><br>DHCP-2 Button<br>PC1 is powered up, and the show i p dhcp binding and show i p dhcp server statistics commands are used again. The binding information now displays that the IP address of 192.168.10.10 has been bound to a MAC address. The statistics are also displaying DHCP DISCOVER, DHCP REQUEST, DHCP OFFER, and DHCP ACK activity.<br><br>DHCP Client Button<br>The i p config/all command issued in the command window on PC1 displays the TCP/IP configured parameters on the DHCP client. Because PC1 was connected to the network segment 192.168.10.0/24, it automatically received an IP address, DNS suffix, and default gateway from that pool. <br><br>DHCP-3 Button<br>After configuring router R1 to provide IP addresses for clients on the 192.168.11.0 LAN, the show i p dhcp binding and show i p dhcp server statistics commands are used again. The binding information now indicates that two hosts have been provided with IP addresses. The PC1 MAC address is bound to IP address 192.168.10.10, and the PC2 MAC address is bound to IP address 192.168.11.10. The DHCP statistics also reflect the exchange of DHCP messages.<br><br>DHCP Pools Button<br>The show i p dhcp pool command summarizes the DHCP pool information for LAN-POOL-1 and LAN-POOL-2. The LAN-POOL-1 address range is 192.168.10.1 to 192.168.10.254. The LAN-POOL-2 address range is 192.168.11.1 to 192.168.11.254. Each pool shows one IP address leased at this time.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
