<transcript lastedited="11.17.08 11:11:43">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[2.2.5  - Establishing a Link with LCP]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts LCP packet codes. The Data field of the LCP frame is expanded to show the fields it contains: Code, Identifier, Length, and Data (various lengths).<br><br>LCP Packet Codes:<br><br>LCP Code: One.<br>LCP Packet Type: Configure-Request.<br>Description: Sent to open or reset a P P P connection. Configure-Request contains a list of LCP options with changes to default option values.<br><br>LCP Code: Two.<br>LCP Packet Type: Configure-Ack.<br>Description: Sent when all the values of all the LCP options in the last Configure-Request received are recognized and acceptable. When both P P P peers send and receive Configure-Acks, the LCP negotiation is complete.<br><br>LCP Code: Three.<br>LCP Packet Type: Configure-Nack.<br>Description: Sent when all the LCP options are recognized, but the values of some options are not acceptable. Configure-Nack includes the offending options and their acceptable values.<br><br>LCP Code: Four.<br>LCP Packet Type: Configure-Reject.<br>Description: Sent when LCP options are not recognized or not acceptable for negotiation. Configure-Reject includes the unrecognized or non-negotiable options.<br><br>LCP Code: Five.<br>LCP Packet Type: Terminate-Request.<br>Description: Optionally sent to close the P P P connection.<br><br>LCP Code: Six.<br>LCP Packet Type: Terminate-Ack.<br>Description: Sent in response to the Terminate-Request.<br><br>LCP Code: Seven.<br>LCP Packet Type: Code-Reject.<br>Description: Sent when the LCP code is unknown. The Code-Reject message includes the offending LCP packet.<br><br>LCP Code: Eight.<br>LCP Packet Type: Protocol-Reject.<br>Description: Sent when the P P P frame contains an unknown Protocol ID. The Protocol-Reject message includes the offending LCP packet. Protocol-Reject is typically sent by a P P P peer in response to a P P P NCP for a LAN protocol not enabled on the P P P peer.<br><br>LCP Code: Nine.<br>LCP Packet Type: Echo-Request.<br>Description: Optionally sent to test the P P P connection.<br><br>LCP Code: Ten.<br>LCP Packet Type: Echo-Reply.<br>Description: Sent in response to an Echo-Request. The P P P Echo-Request and Echo-Reply are not related to the ICMP Echo Request and Echo Reply messages.<br><br>LCP Code: Eleven.<br>LCP Packet Type: Discard-Request.<br>Description: Optionally sent to exercise the link in the outbound direction.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
