<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 19:11:07">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.1.6  - The Enterprise Security Policy]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple activities.<br><br>Activity One:<br>In this activity, you select the appropriate word or phrase to fill in the BLANK or BLANKS and complete the sentence. Not all answers are used, and some answers may be used more then once.<br><br>Sentences:<br>One. BLANK is a general term that has historically been used to describe a computer programming expert.<br><br>Two. BLANK is generally regarded as the more accurate term to describe someone who tries to gain unauthorized access to network resources with malicious intent.<br><br>Three. BLANK is a term used to describe an individual that manipulates the phone network to cause it to perform a function that is normally not allowed.<br><br>Four. BLANK is a term used to describe an individual that sends large quantities of unsolicited email messages.<br><br>Five. BLANK is a term used to describe an individual that uses email or other means in an attempt to trick others into providing sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or passwords.<br><br>Six. BLANK is a term used to describe individuals that use their abilities to find vulnerabilities in systems or networks, and then report these vulnerabilities to the owners of the system so that they can be fixed.<br><br>Seven. BLANK is another term for individuals that use their knowledge of computer systems to break into systems or networks that they are not authorized to use.<br><br>Words:<br>A: White hat.<br>B: Hacker.<br>C: Phreaker.<br>D: Spammer.<br>E: Cracker.<br>F: Phisher.<br>G: Black hat.<br><br>Activity Two:<br>In this activity, you identify the type of attack represented by the example given. <br>Attack Examples:<br>One. Email bombs.<br>Two. Internet information queries.<br>Three. Man-in-the-middle attack.<br>Four. Packet sniffers.<br>Five. Password attacks.<br>Six. Ping of death.<br>Seven. Ping sweeps.<br>Eight. Port scans.<br><br>Attack Type:<br>Reconnaissance attacks.<br>Access attacks.<br>D o S and D D o S attacks.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
