<transcript lastedited="01.08.09 13:01:30">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.3.7 - IPSec Security Protocols]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts a simulation activity in which you configure a central and branch routers to provide a site-to-site IPSec VPN. Read the scenario and match the proper values to the entries in the Linksys Web interface screen for each VPN device.<br><br>Note: You may wish to contact your instructor for assistance in performing this activity.<br><br>Scenario:<br>A small company has set up Internet connectivity using two Linksys WRVS 4400 N business class routers. One is located at the central site and the other at the branch site. The company would like to access resources between sites, but they are concerned that the Internet traffic would not be secure. To address this concern, it has been suggested that the company implements a site-to-site VPN between the two sites. A VPN would enable the branch site office to connect to the central site office securely by creating a VPN tunnel that encrypts and decrypts data.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Central Site:<br>- PC1 is connected to the central site router on the 192.168.1.0/24 network.<br>- The central site router LAN interface IP address is 192.168.1.1.<br>- The central site router Internet VPN interface IP address is 209.165.200.225.<br><br>Branch Site:<br>- PC2 is connected to the branch site router on the 192.168.101.0/24 network.<br>- The branch site router LAN interface IP address is 192.168.101.1.<br>- The branch site router Internet VPN interface IP address is 209.165.202.129.<br><br>Referencing the topology description above, fill in the blanks to configure the settings and enable a VPN called Site-to-Site using MD5 authentication, 3D E S encryption, and a pre-shared key of cisco 1 2 3. Select from the choices listed below for both the central site and branch site routers.<br><br>Required Configuration Entries:<br><br>Central Site Linksys router:<br>IPSec VPN Tunnel Name: BLANK<br>Local Security Group IP Address: BLANK<br>Remote Security Group IP Address: BLANK<br>Remote Security Gateway IP Address: BLANK<br>Key Management Encryption: BLANK<br>Key Management Authentication: BLANK<br>Key Management Pre-Shared Key: BLANK<br><br>Branch Site Linksys router:<br>IPSec VPN Tunnel Name: BLANK<br>Local Security Group IP Address: BLANK<br>Remote Security Group IP Address: BLANK<br>Remote Security Gateway IP Address: BLANK<br>Key Management Encryption: BLANK<br>Key Management Authentication: BLANK<br>Key Management Pre-Shared Key: BLANK<br><br>Entry choices for both routers: <br>MD5<br>Site-to-Site<br>192.168.101.0<br>209.165.202.129<br>192.168.1.0<br>3D E S<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>cisco 1 2 3<br>192.168.1.1<br>192.168.101.0<br>209.165.200.0<br>209.165.200.255<br>209.165.202.0<br>D E S<br>A E S<br>S H A<br>Remote Access]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
