<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 13:12:54">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[8.4.6 - Application Layer Troubleshooting]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts an Application Layer overview. The seven layers of the O S I model are shown with the top three layers highlighted: Application, Presentation, and Session. The TCP/IP model is shown next to it. The TCP/IP layers are mapped to their corresponding O S I layers. The TCP/IP protocols that operate at each layer in the TCP/IP model are identified. Also shown is a tabular listing of application protocols and ports.<br><br>Application Layer Overview:<br>TCP Application Layer: Corresponds to O S I layers 5, 6, and 7. Applications and protocols include HTTP, Telnet, FTP, TFTP, SMTP, POP, I MAP, SNMP, NTP, DNS, and NNTP. NFS, XDR, and RPC are also shown at this layer.<br><br>TCP Transport Layer: Corresponds to O S I Layer 4. Protocols include TCP and UDP.<br><br>TCP Internet Layer: Corresponds to O S I Layer 3. Protocols include routing protocols, IP, and ICMP.<br><br>TCP Network Access Layer: Corresponds to O S I layers 1 and 2. Protocols include ARP and RARP. The Physical Layer is not specified with the TCP/IP model.<br><br>Application Protocols and Ports<br><br>Application: WWW browser<br>Protocol and Port: HTTP (TCP port 80)<br>Description: HTTP is used by Web browsers and servers to transfer the files that make up web pages.<br><br>Application: File transfer<br>Protocol and Port: FTP (TCP ports 20 and 21)<br>Description: FTP provides a way to move files between computer systems.<br><br>Application: Terminal emulation<br>Protocol and Port: Telnet (TCP port 23)<br>Description: Telnet provides terminal emulation services over a reliable TCP stream.<br><br>Application: Electronic mail<br>Protocol and Port: POP3 (TCP port 110)<br>SMTP (TCP port 25)<br>I MAP 4 (TCP port 143)<br>Description: Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP) transfers electronic mail between mail servers. It is used by mail clients to send mail. Mail clients use either the Post Office Protocol version 3 (POP3) or the Internet Message Access Protocol (I MAP) to receive mail.<br><br>Application: Network management<br>Protocol and Port: SNMP (UDP port 161)<br>Description: The Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) reports anomalous network conditions and sets network threshold values.<br><br>Application: Distributed File Service<br>Protocol and Port: X Windows (UDP ports 6000-6063)<br>NFS, XDR, RPC (UDP port 111)<br>Description: X Windows is a popular protocol that permits intelligent terminals to communicate with remote computers as if they were directly attached. NFS, external data representation (XDR), and remote-procedure call (RPC) combine to allow transparent access to remote network resources.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
