<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 19:11:12">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.1.3  - Types of Network Attacks]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts four types of access attacks: password attacks, trust exploitation, port redirection, and man-in-the-middle.<br><br>Password Attack:<br>An authorization screenshot is shown for entering a username and password. Attackers can implement password attacks using several different methods:<br>- Brute-force attacks.<br>- Trojan horse programs.<br>- Packet sniffers.<br><br>Trust Exploitation:<br>The diagram shows an attacker and PC's labeled System A and System B connected to a firewall. Network OS's and trust models are shown as follows:<br>Windows: Domains Active Directory (A D)<br>Linux and UNIX: Network File System (NFS) Network Information Service Plus (N I S +).<br> <br>In this animation, the attacker's goal is to gain access to System A. When the animation is run, the attacker cannot get access to System A, but notices that he can gain access to System B. Because System B trusts everyone, the attacker now has access to System A through the access gained from System B. <br><br>Port Redirection:<br>The diagram shows an attacker accessing and compromising Host A on port 22 (SSH). Host A then accesses Host B on behalf of the attacker on Port 23 (Telnet). <br><br>Port redirection is a type of trust-exploitation attack that uses a compromised host to pass traffic through a firewall that would otherwise be dropped. It is mitigated primarily through using proper trust models. Antivirus software and host-based I D S can help detect and prevent an attacker installing port-redirecting utilities on the host.<br><br>Man-in-the-Middle:<br>The diagram shows an attacker with a PC acting as a man-in-the-middle by intercepting a web page request and altering it to take advantage of the victim. In the example, the victim unknowingly clicks a link in a phish email. The following process is described:<br><br>One. When a victim requests a web page, the victim's host makes the request to the attacker's host.<br><br>Two. The attacker's host receives the request and fetches the real page from the legitimate website. <br><br>Three. The attacker can alter the legitimate webpage and apply any transformations to the data desired. <br><br>Four. The attacker forwards the requested page to the victim.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
