<transcript lastedited="11.25.08 19:11:31">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[4.1.3  - Types of Network Attacks]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts five types of D o S related attacks. These include the D o S Attack, Ping of Death, SYN Flood, D D o S, and Smurf Attack.<br><br>D o S Attack:<br>The diagram shows an attacker with a PC sending excessive amounts of traffic to a server and using up system resources, thus preventing authorized people from using a service. Types of resource overloads and malformed data are listed:<br><br>Resource overloads:<br>Disk space, bandwidth, buffers.<br>Ping floods such as smurf.<br>Packet storms such as UDP bombs and fraggle.<br><br>Malformed data:<br>Oversized packets such as ping of death.<br>Overlapping packets such as winuke.<br>Unhandled data such as teardrop.<br><br>Ping of Death:<br>The animation shows an attacker with a PC sending the ping of death and disabling a computer.<br><br>SYN Flood:<br>The diagram shows an attacker with a PC sending multiple SYN requests to a web server. The web server sends multiple SYN-Ack replies and waits to complete the three-way handshake. A valid user sends a SYN request, but the server is unable to respond.<br><br>D D o S:<br>The diagram shows a client PC who launches an attack from a PC to several handler PC's. A handler is a compromised host that is running the attacker program. Each handler controls multiple agents or zombies. <br>The agents are compromised hosts running the attacker program. They are responsible for generating streams of packets directed toward the intended victim.<br><br>Smurf Attack:<br>The diagram shows an attacker creating an echo request and using a smurf amplifier to send to many zombie computers. The zombies send echo replies to the victim in an attempt to overwhelm the WAN link to the destination. <br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
