<transcript lastedited="01.13.09 13:01:08">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[2.1.4  - D T E and DCE]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts various WAN cabling standards. Information is provided for a null modem, serial cable types, DB-60 connectors, smart serial connectors, and router-to-router connections.<br><br>Null Modem:<br>The diagram shows two DB-9 connectors. The pins used to create a null modem are connected between the two D T E's. Pin 5 (signal ground) on Connector One is connected to Pin 5 (signal ground) on Connector Two. Pin 2 (receive data) on Connector One is connected to Pin 3 (send data) on Connector Two. Pin 3 (send data) on Connector One is connected to Pin 2 (receive data) on Connector Two.<br><br>Serial Cables:<br>The diagram shows various WAN serial cables and connectors connecting D T E (router) and DCE (CSU/DSU) devices. These include EIA/T IA-232, EIA/T IA-449, V.35, X.21, and EIA-530.<br><br>DB-60 connector:<br>An older style DB-60 connector, the router end of the DCE/D T E connection, is shown.<br><br>Smart Serial connectors:<br>The diagram shows a smart serial cable and WAN interface card (WIC-2T) with two smart serial connectors. This supports higher port densities in a smaller form factor. The router interface end of the smart serial cable is a 26-pin connector that is significantly more compact than the DB-60 connector.<br><br>Router-to-Router connections:<br>The smart serial cables are used to provide a router-to-router DCE to D T E connection. <br><br>On the left side of the diagram, two PC's are connected to a hub that is connected to a router. This router interface is acting as the DCE. A smart serial cable with a small 26-pin connector attaches to the router interface. The other end of the cable is a female DCE V.35 connector. <br><br>On the right side of the diagram, two PC's are connected to a hub that is connected to a router. This router interface is acting as the D T E. A smart serial cable with a small 26-pin connector attaches to the router interface. The other end of the cable is a male D T E V.35 connector. <br><br>The smart serial female DCE V.35 connector connects to the smart serial male D T E V.35 connector to complete the link between the routers. This effectively eliminates the CSU/DSU's to simulate a WAN link.<br><br>A diagram of the cable wiring shows that the DCE cable transmit and receive pins are wired as Tx to Tx and Rx to Rx. The D T E cable transmit and receive pins are wired as Tx to Rx and Rx to Tx.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
