<transcript lastedited="11.17.08 08:11:26">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[1.3.5  - Internet Connection Options]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts VPN technology, including site-to-site VPN's and remote access VPN's. <br><br>Site-to-Site VPN's:<br>Three buildings are shown, the company head office, Branch Office A, and Branch Office B. The company head office building contains a VPN gateway or concentrator. One side of the gateway is connected to an external router and the other to an internal router. The internal router is connected to a switch and an Intranet Web/TFTP server. The external router is connected to router ISP A for access to the Internet.<br><br>Branch Office A contains a LAN and a router connected to ISP C on the Internet. Branch Office B contains a LAN and a router connected to ISP B on the Internet.<br><br>A site-to-site VPN tunnel is set up between the company head office router through ISP A to the Internet to ISP B and then to the Branch Office B router. <br><br>Another site-to-site VPN tunnel is set up between the company head office router through ISP A to the Internet to ISP C and then to the Branch Office A router. <br><br>Remote-Access VPN's:<br>The company head office building contains a VPN gateway or concentrator. One side is connected to an external router and the other to an internal router. The internal router is connected to a switch and an Intranet Web/TFTP server. The external router is connected to ISP A for access to the Internet.<br><br>Teleworker One connects to the ISP using DSL. Teleworker Two connects to the ISP using a cable modem. A remote access VPN tunnel is established from the Teleworker One PC, through the ISP router, to the router at the company head office building, and then to the VPN gateway. A VPN client is installed on the PC that requires a user name and password to gain access to the VPN.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
