<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:25">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[2.2.6  - NCP Explained]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple activities. <br><br>Activity One: Match labels to the proper location in the P P P Layer architecture diagram.<br>Labels:<br>- Simultaneous.<br>- Asynchronous.<br>- IP.<br>- IPCP.<br>- IPCXCP.<br>- Multiplexing.<br>- Data Link Layer.<br>- Synchronous.<br>- Link Control Protocol.<br>- Authentication.<br>- IPX.<br>- Network Control Protocol.<br>- Physical Layer.<br>- Transport Layer.<br>- Network Layer.<br><br>Note: Contact your instructor to discuss how best to perform this activity.<br><br>Activity Two: Indicate whether the characteristic describes LCP or NCP. <br>Characteristics:<br>A. Negotiates and sets up control options on the WAN data link.<br>B. Carries packets from several network layer protocols.<br>C. Main role is to establish, configure, and test the data-link connection.<br>D. Terminates the link.<br>E. Brings the network layer protocols up and down.<br>F. Determines when a link is functioning properly or when it is failing.<br>G. Encapsulates and negotiates options for IP and IPX.<br><br>Activity Three: Organize the labels in the order that they appear in the P P P frame format from left to right. Not all labels are used.<br>- MAC.<br>- Flag.<br>- Protocol ID.<br>- Control.<br>- FCS.<br>- Address.<br>- Data Packet.<br><br>Activity Four: Select the proper word or phrase to fill in the BLANK and complete the sentence. Not all answers are used.<br>Sentences:<br>A. P P P uses the BLANK protocol as a basis for encapsulation datagrams over point-to-point links.<br>B. BLANK is used by P P P to establish, configure, and test the data link connection.<br>C. BLANK is used by P P P to establish and configure different network layer protocols.<br>D. The binary sequence for the address field in a P P P frame is BLANK.<br>E. The link establishment phase is complete when a configuration BLANK frame has been sent and received.<br>F. IPCP negotiates two options: compression and BLANK assignments.<br>G. When the NCP process is complete, the link goes into the BLANK state, and LCP takes over again.<br><br>Word or phrase:<br>- Active.<br>- LCP.<br>- Acknowledgement.<br>- HDLC.<br>- Open.<br>- Link quality.<br>- NCP.<br>- 11111111.<br>- Authentication.<br>- IP address.<br>- 01111110.<br>- Request.<br>- SDLC.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
