<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 11:12:22">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.5.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.A technician is attempting to explain broadband technology to a customer. Which two descriptions or examples should be used to educate the customer? (Choose two.)<br>A.Includes dialup connections using POTS.<br>B.Incompatible with multiplexing.<br>C.Uses a wide band of frequencies.<br>D.Offer sustained speeds of 128k or more.<br>E.Requires line-of-sight connection with the service provider.<br><br>2.When accommodating a teleworker, which type of connection should be used when mobile access during traveling is required and broadband options are unavailable?<br>A.Residential cable<br>B.DSL<br>C.Dialup<br>D.Satellite<br><br>3.When comparing DOCSIS and Euro-DOCSIS, what is the primary difference between the two specifications?<br>A.Flow control mechanisms<br>B.Maximum data rates<br>C.Access methods<br>D.Channel bandwidths<br><br>4.If asked to describe DSL technology, which three statements would help the user develop a better understanding of the technology? (Choose three.)<br>A.DSL is available in any location that has a telephone.<br>B.A DSL typically has a higher download bandwidth than available upload bandwidth.<br>C.In home installation, a splitter separates the A DSL and voice signals at the N ID, allowing multiple A DSL outlets in the house.<br>D.DSL speeds can exceed the speeds available with a typical T1 line.<br>E.Transfer rates vary by the length of the local loop.<br>F.All varieties of DSL provide the same bandwidth, although they use different technologies to achieve upload and download.<br><br>5.In a DSL installation, which two devices are installed at the customer site? (Choose two.)<br>A.CM<br>B.DOCSIS<br>C.D SLAM<br>D.Microfilter<br>E.DSL transceiver<br><br>6.Refer to the topology description below to answer the question.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Three locations connect to the corporate network through the Internet cloud.<br>Corporate Network - A VPN concentrator and PIX appliance connect to Router R10, which connects to the Internet cloud.<br>Business Partner - Switch SW1 connects to router R1, which connects to the Internet cloud. <br>Remote Office - Switch SW2 connects to router R2, which connects to the Internet cloud. <br>Regional Office - Switch SW3 connects to a PIX appliance, which connects to the Internet cloud. <br><br>On the basis of the network topology above, which devices or software applications provide encapsulation and encryption for the VPN traffic?<br>A.VPN client software installed on the machines of the users at the regional office only.<br>B.PIX appliances at the corporate network and regional office only.<br>C.Router and PIX appliance at the corporate network, and the routers and PIX appliance at all remote locations.<br>D.LAN switches and routers at the remote locations only.<br><br>7.Which two techniques can be used to secure the traffic sent over a VPN connection? (Choose two.)<br>A.Data labeling to mark and separate the VPN traffic for different customers.<br>B.Data encapsulation to transmit data transparently from network to network through a shared network infrastructure.<br>C.Data encryption to code data into a different format using a secret key.<br>D.Second routing protocol to transport the traffic over the VPN tunnel.<br>E.Dedicated connection over the company's private leased line.<br><br>8.Match the description on the left with the corresponding VPN characteristic on the right.<br>Descriptions:<br>A. Uses passwords, digital certificates, smart cards, and biometrics.<br>B. Prevents tampering and alterations to data while data travels between the source and destination.<br>C. Protects the contents of messages from interception by unauthenticated or unauthorized sources.<br>D. Uses hashes.<br>E. Ensures that the communicating peers are who they say they are.<br>F. Uses encapsulation and encryption.<br><br>Characteristics:<br>One. Data Confidentiality<br>Two. Data Integrity<br>Three. Authentication<br><br>9.Which is an example of a tunneling protocol developed by Cisco?<br>A.A E S<br>B.D E S<br>C.RSA<br>D.ESP<br>E.GRE<br><br>10.Match the description to the corresponding type of tunneling protocol.<br>Descriptions:<br>A. Frame Relay, ATM, MPLS.<br>B. The protocol that is wrapped around the original data.<br>C. The protocol over which the original data was being carried.<br>D. IPX, AppleTalk, IPv4, IPv6.<br>E. GRE, IPSec, L2F, P P T P, L2TP.<br>F. The protocol over which the information is traveling.<br><br>Type of Tunneling Protocol:<br>One. Carrier Protocol<br>Encapsulating Protocol<br>Passenger Protocol<br><br>11.Match the description to the correct algorithm.<br>Descriptions:<br>A. Encryption and decryption use the same key.<br>B. Public key cryptography.<br>C. Encryption and decryption use different keys.<br>D. D E S, 3D E S, A E S<br>E. RSA<br>F. Shared secret key cryptology<br><br>One. Algorithm categories<br>Two. Symmetric algorithm<br>Three. Asymmetric algorithm<br><br>12.What type of connection is the most cost-effective to adequately support a SOHO teleworker to access the Internet?<br>A.Direct T1 link to the Internet<br>B.56k dialup<br>C.One-way multicast satellite Internet system<br>D.DSL to an ISP<br><br>13.Which wireless standard operates in both licensed and unlicensed bands of the spectrum from 2 to 8 GHz and allows for transmission rates of 70 Mbps at a range of up to 50 kilometers?<br>A.8 0 2 dot 11g<br>B.8 0 2 dot 11n<br>C.8 0 2 dot 11b<br>D.8 0 2 dot 16<br>E.8 0 2 dot 11e<br><br>14.What is typically deployed to support high-speed transmissions of data to SOHO cable modems?<br>A.Hybrid fiber-coaxial (HFC)<br>B.High-speed dialup cable modems<br>C.Broadband copper coaxial<br>D.1000 Base TX]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
