<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 11:12:31">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.2.2 - Cable]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts the structure of a cable system. Rollover text provides additional information on each component.<br><br>- CATV originally meant community antenna television. This form of transmission shared TV signals.<br>- Cable systems were originally built to extend the reach of TV signals and improve over-the-air TV reception.<br>- Modern cable systems use fiber and coaxial for signal transmission.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>A building location labeled Headend is the main component in the cable transportation system. An antenna site receives TV signals and passes them to the headend for distribution. A trunk cable carries the signal from the headend to the first amplifier. Other amplifiers boost the signal as it travels to various houses along the way. A distribution cable feeds a home, and a subscriber drop cable carries the signal into the home.<br><br>Rollover text provides additional information on cable system components.<br><br>Antenna Site: <br>The location of an antenna site is chosen for optimum reception of over-the-air, satellite, and sometimes point-to-point signals. The main receiving antennas and satellite dishes are located at the antenna site.<br><br>Headend: <br>This is where signals are first received, processed, formatted, and then distributed downstream to the cable network. The headend facility is usually not staffed, under security fencing, and is similar to a telephone company central office.<br><br>Distribution Network: <br>In a classic cable system called a tree-and-branch cable system, the distribution network consists of trunk and feeder cables. The trunk is the backbone that distributes signals throughout the community service area to the feeder and typically uses 0.750 inch (19 millimeter) diameter coaxial cable. The feeder branches flow from a trunk and reach all the subscribers in the service area via coaxial cables. The feeder cable is usually a 0.50 inch (13 millimeter) diameter coaxial cable. <br><br>Subscriber Drop: <br>A subscriber drop connects the subscriber to the cable services. The subscriber drop is a connection between the feeder part of a distribution network and the subscriber terminal device (for example, TV set, videocassette recorder [VCR], high-definition TV set-top box, or cable modem). A subscriber drop consists of radio grade (RG) coaxial cabling (usually 59-series or 6-series coaxial cable), grounding and attachment hardware, passive devices, and a set-top box.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
