<transcript lastedited="11.21.08 08:11:16">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.2.2  - Configuring Static Basic Frame Relay Maps]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts configuring a static Frame Relay map. Information is provided on parameters and verification.<br><br>Network Topology:<br>There are four routers, R1, R2, ISP, and Frame Relay Switch. Routers R1 and R2 are connected to Frame Relay Switch in the cloud. R2 is also connected to the ISP with a dedicated link. <br><br>Router R1 S0/0/1 with IP address 10.1.1.1 /30 is connected to Frame Relay Switch S0/0/0 (DCE).<br><br>Router R2 S0/0/1 with IP address 10.1.1.2 /30 is connected to Frame Relay Switch S0/0/1 (DCE).<br><br>Router R2 L o 0 with IP address 209.165.200.225 /27 simulates the connection to the ISP router. <br><br>Static Frame Relay Maps<br>To map between a next hop protocol address and a DLCI destination address, use the following command syntax:<br><br>frame-relay map protocol protocol-address dlci [broadcast].<br><br>R1 Static Map Configuration:<br>interface s 0/0/1<br>i p address 10.1.1.1 255.255.255.252<br>encapsulation frame-relay<br>bandwidth 64<br>frame-relay map i p 10.1.1.2 broadcast<br><br>Parameters:<br><br>Command Parameter: protocol.<br>Description: Defines the supported protocol, bridging, or logical link control: appletalk, decnet, dlsw, i p, i p x, l l c 2, rsrb, vines, and xns.<br><br>Command Parameter: protocol-address.<br>Description: Defines the Network Layer address of the destination router interface.<br><br>Command Parameter: dlci.<br>Description: Defines the local DLCI used to connect to the remote protocol address.<br><br>Command Parameter: broadcast.<br>Description: (Optional) Allows broadcasts and multicasts over the VC. This permits the use of dynamic routing protocols over the VC.<br><br>Verification:<br>Router R1 show frame-relay map command output:<br>R1 #show frame-relay map<br>Serial 0/0/1 (up): i p 10.1.1.2 dlci 102 (0 x 66, 0 x1860), static, broadcast, CISCO, status defined, active<br><br>Router R2 show frame-relay map command output:<br>R2# show frame-relay map<br>Serial 0/0/1 (up): i p 10.1.1.1 dlci 201 (0 x c 9, 0 x 3090), static, broadcast, CISCO, status defined, active<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
