<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 08:12:28">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[5.3.2 - Configuring Extended ACL's]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts extended ACL access-list command syntax. Parameters are listed along with a description of what they do. An example of an extended ACL application is also shown.<br><br>Extended ACL Command Syntax:<br><br>The full syntax of the extended ACL command is as follows: <br><br>Access-list access-list-number {deny | permit | remark} protocol source [source-wildcard] [operator operand] ]port port-number or name] destination [destination-wildcard] [operator operand] [port port-number or name] [established]<br><br>Parameter: access-list-number<br>Description: Identifies the access list using a number in the range of 100 to 199 for an extended IP ACL, and 2000 to 2699 for expanded IP ACL's.<br><br>Parameter: deny<br>Description: Denies access if the conditions are matched.<br><br>Parameter: permit<br>Description: Permits access if the conditions are matched.<br><br>Parameter: remark<br>Description: Indicates whether this entry allows or blocks the specified address. Could also be used to enter a remark.<br><br>Parameter: protocol<br>Description: Name or number of an Internet protocol. Common keywords include icmp, i p, TCP, or UDP. To match any Internet protocol, including ICMP, TCP, and UDP, use the i p keyword.<br><br>Parameter: source<br>Description: Number of the network or host from which the packet is being sent.<br><br>Parameter: source-wildcard<br>Description: Wildcard bits to be applied to the source.<br><br>Parameter: destination<br>Description: Number of the network or host to which the packet is being sent.<br><br>Parameter: destination-wildcard<br>Description: Wildcard bits to be applied to the destination.<br><br>Parameter: operator<br>Description: (Optional) Compares source or destination ports. Possible operands include l t (less than), g t (greater than), e q (equal), n e q (not equal), and range (inclusive range).<br><br>Parameter: port<br>Description: (Optional) The decimal number or name of a TCP or UDP port.<br><br>Parameter: established<br>Description: (Optional) For the TCP protocol only. Indicates an established connection.<br><br>Configuring Extended ACL's:<br><br>Network Topology:<br>Two LAN's, 192.168.10.0/24 and 192.168.11.0/24, are attached to routers R1 and R3, respectively. R1 and R3 are interconnected by router R2. <br>Router R2 has a L o 0 interface simulating the ISP.<br><br>R1(config)#access-list 103 permit tcp 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255 any e q 80<br>R1(config)#access-list 103 permit tcp 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255 any e q 443<br>R1(config)#access-list 104 permit tcp any 192.168.10.0 0.0.0.255 established<br><br>ACL 103 allows to ports 80 and 443.<br>ACL 104 allows established HTTP and HTTPS replies.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
