<transcript lastedited="11.21.08 08:11:04">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.1.2  - Virtual Circuits]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple VC's on a single access line. A group of switches is interconnected in a Frame Relay cloud. Four routers are shown, each connected to a Frame Relay switch at the edge of the cloud. One router is unlabeled. The others are labeled R1, R2, and R6.<br><br>Single Access Line:<br>Router R1 connects to its Frame Relay edge switch using a single physical access link, but there are two DLCI's multiplexed on the link. These are DLCI 102 and DLCI 319. DLCI 102 provides a VC through the Frame Relay switch cloud to router R6, and DLCI 319 provides a VC through the cloud to router R2. The data destined for these two different locations is interleaved on a single link until it reaches a switch where it splits and is routed to another part of the Frame Relay network to reach the final destination.<br><br>Span Engineering's DLCI's:<br>The diagram depicts six routers representing the locations or sites of the company Span Engineering. The sites are Chicago (Headquarters), Toronto, New York, Dallas, Mexico City, and San Jose. Each of these has a physical Frame Relay access link to an edge switch in the Frame Relay cloud. All the sites have a single DLCI defined on their access link. The Chicago site (Headquarters) connects to all other sites and has DLCI's defined to reach each of those locations. The data to the other sites is multiplexed on a single physical Frame Relay access link. <br><br>Span Engineering has a DLCI to each location from Chicago:<br><br>Location: New York<br>DLCI: 17<br><br>Location: Toronto<br>DLCI: 18<br><br>Location: Dallas<br>DLCI: 19<br><br>Location: Mexico City<br>DLCI: 20<br><br>Location: San Jose<br>DLCI: 21<br><br>Clicking on the location in the table highlights the VC path through the Frame Relay switches in the cloud.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
