<transcript lastedited="01.08.09 13:01:56">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[7.2.8 - Verifying and Troubleshooting NAT Configurations]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts verifying NAT and NAT Overload with various examples, including NAT Overload, NAT translations, NAT statistics, and cleared NAT.<br><br>NAT Overload:<br>The diagram shows two PC's connected to the inside network cloud, which is connected to router R2. Router R2 is connected to the Internet cloud.<br><br>Inside Network:<br>PC1 IP address: 192.168.10.10<br>PC2 IP address: 192.168.10.11<br>Router R2 S0/0/0 interface IP address: 10.1.1.2<br><br>Outside Network:<br>Router R2 S0/1/0 interface IP address: 209.165.200.225<br><br>Router Configuration Commands:<br>access-list 1 permit 192.168.0.0 0.0.255.255<br>i p nat inside source list 1 interface serial0/1/0 overload<br>interface serial0/0/0<br>i p nat inside<br>interface serial0/1/0<br>i p nat outside<br><br>NAT Translations:<br>Output from the show i p nat translations and show i p nat translations verbose commands is displayed. <br><br>Below is a sample of information presented in the show i p nat translations output for NAT overload. The verbose option provides additional details on entries.<br><br>Pro: tcp<br>Inside Global: 209.165.200.225:16642<br>Inside Local: 192.168.10.10:16642<br>Outside Local IP Address: 209.165.200.254:80<br>Outside Global: 209.165.200.254:80<br><br>Pro: tcp<br>Inside Global: 209.165.200.225:62452<br>Inside Local: 192.168.11.10:62452<br>Outside Local IP Address: 209.165.200.254:80<br>Outside Global: 209.165.200.254:80<br><br>NAT Statistics:<br>Output from the show i p nat translations and show i p nat statistics commands is displayed. <br><br>Below is a sample of information presented in the show i p nat statistics output for NAT overload.<br>R2#show i p nat statistics<br>Total active translations: 3 (0 static, 3 dynamic; 3 extended)<br>Outside interfaces:<br>  Serial0/1/0<br>Inside interfaces:<br>  Serial0/0/0, Serial0/0/1<br>Hits: 173 Misses: 9<br>CEF Translated packets: 182, CEF Punted packets: 0<br>Expired translations: 6<br>Dynamic mappings:<br>-- Inside Source<br>[Id: 1] access-list 1 interface Serial0/1/0 ref count 3<br>Queued Packets: 0<br>R2#<br><br>Cleared NAT:<br>The clear i p nat translation * command clears the NAT table of entries. Output from the show i p nat translations now displays no output.<br><br>Syntax for the clear i p nat translation command:<br>Command: clear i p nat translation *<br>Description: Clears all dynamic address translation entries from the NAT translation table.<br><br>Command: clear i p nat translation inside global-i p local-i p [outside local-i p global-i p]<br>Description: Clears a simple dynamic translation entry containing an inside translation or both inside and outside translations.<br><br>Command: clear i p nat translation protocol inside global-i p global-port local-i p local-port [outside local-i p local-port global-i p global-port]<br>Description: Clears an extended dynamic translation entry.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
