<transcript lastedited="11.17.08 08:11:31">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[1.3.2  - Dedicated Connection Link Options]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts a leased line WAN topology and a table of line types with bit rate capacity.<br><br>Leased Line WAN Topology:<br>Two buildings, the New York office and the London office, are connected through a WAN service provider.<br><br>A router in the New York office connects to a CSU/DSU, which then connects to a T3 link, a standard in the U.S. The T3 link connects to the service provider's network cloud.<br><br>A router in the London office connects to a CSU/DSU, which then connects to an E3 link, a standard in Europe. The E3 link connects to the service provider's network cloud.<br><br>Line Types and Bandwidth (Bit Rate Capacity):<br><br>Line Type: 56, Bit Rate Capacity: 56 kilobits per second.<br>Line Type: 64, Bit Rate Capacity: 64 kilobits per second.<br>Line Type: T1, Bit Rate Capacity: 1.544 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: E1, Bit Rate Capacity:  2.048 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: J1, Bit Rate Capacity:   2.048 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: E3, Bit Rate Capacity:  34.064 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: T3, Bit Rate Capacity:  44.736 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-1, Bit Rate Capacity: 51.84 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-3, Bit Rate Capacity: 155.54 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-9, Bit Rate Capacity: 466.56 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-12, Bit Rate Capacity: 622.08 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-18, Bit Rate Capacity: 933.12 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-24, Bit Rate Capacity: 1244.16 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-36, Bit Rate Capacity: 1866.24 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-48, Bit Rate Capacity: 2488.32 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-96, Bit Rate Capacity: 4976.64 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-192, Bit Rate Capacity: 9953.28 Megabits per second.<br>Line Type: O C-768, Bit Rate Capacity: 39813.12 Megabits per second.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
