<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 11:12:03">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.2.1 - Connecting Teleworkers to the WAN]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts various last-mile access technologies that allow teleworkers to connect to the WAN. These include the following:<br><br>Dialup access - The customer is connected using a dialup modem and a phone line to connect to a POP at ISP A, which is a telephone company.<br><br>With access speeds around 56 Kbps, dialup access is the slowest connection option. For example, downloading a 5 MB file using a 56 Kbps dialup connection takes approximately twelve minutes.<br><br>DSL access - The customer is connected using a DSL modem and a phone line to connect to a POP at ISP A.<br><br>DSL provides high-speed broadband access at speeds of 200 Kbps and higher. Upload and download speeds vary with distance from the central office.<br>There are many types of DSL. Home users usually use asymmetric DSL (ADSL), which has download speeds higher than upload speeds. Symmetric DSL (SDSL) has the same speeds up and down. SDSL is more suitable for small-to-medium business applications.<br><br>Cable modem access - The customer is connected using a cable modem and a coaxial cable to connect to a POP at ISP B, which is a cable service provider.<br><br>Cable is similar to DSL in that it provides broadband access at speeds of 200 Kbps and higher. Unlike DSL, speeds are not affected by the distance to the ISP. However, cable is a shared service, so speeds are affected to a degree by the number of subscribers sharing a particular lag of the distribution network.<br><br>Satellite access - The customer is connected using a satellite modem and a wireless link through a satellite to connect to a POP at ISP C, which is a satellite service provider.<br><br>Satellite Internet access speeds range from 128 Kbps to 512 Kbps, depending on the subscriber plan.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
