<transcript lastedited="11.21.08 08:11:50">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.3.3  - Frame Relay Flow Control]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple activities.<br><br>Activity One - Solving Reachability Issues: In this activity, select the appropriate word or phrase to fill in the BLANK or BLANKs and complete the sentence. Not all answers are used.<br><br>Sentences:<br>A.	Frame Relay networks are usually built in a BLANK topology, which can cause reachability Issues. <br>B.	Split horizon is a technique used to prevent BLANK in networks that use distance vector protocols.<br>C.	Solving reachability issues requires using a BLANK topology, which is expensive, or using BLANK.<br>D.	In BLANK configurations, a single subinterface is used to establish one PVC connection to another physical or subinterface on a remote router.<br>E.	In BLANK configurations, a single subinterface is used to establish multiple PVC connections to multiple physical interfaces or subinterfaces on remote routers.<br>F.	The BLANK command is configured on the physical interface. All other configuration items, such as the Network Layer address and DLCI's, are configured on the subinterfaces.<br><br><br>Words:<br>hub-and-spoke.<br>encapsulation frame-relay.<br>full mesh.<br>broadcasts.<br>partial mesh.<br>subinterfaces.<br>more routers.<br>multiple interfaces.<br>routing loops.<br>multipoint.<br>point-to-point.<br><br>Activity Two - Frame Relay Bandwidth and Flow Control: In this activity, match the term to the appropriate definition. <br><br>Definitions:<br>A.	Maximum number of bits the network guarantees to deliver under normal circumstances.<br>B.	Difference between the guaranteed rate and the maximum rate allowed by the service provider.<br>C.	When a Frame Relay switch experiences congestion, it sets these bits on every frame it receives.<br>D.	Rate at which the service provider agrees to accept bits on the VC.<br>E.	A direct notification stating that there is congestion.<br>F.	An indirect notification that there is congestion.<br>G.	This bit is set if the frame received pushes the counter over the committed burst.<br><br>Terms:<br>BECN.<br>Committed Information Rate (C I R).<br>Discard Eligibility (D E).<br>Committed Burst (B C).<br>Excess Information Rate (E I R).<br>Explicit Congestion Notification (ECN).<br>FECN.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
