<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:57">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.1.5  - Frame Relay Address Mapping]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts multiple activities.<br><br>Activity One: In this activity, select the appropriate word or phrase to fill in the BLANK or BLANKs and complete the sentence. Not all answers are used, and some answers may be used more than once.<br><br>Sentences:<br>A.Frame Relay has become the most widely used WAN technology, primarily for its BLANK and BLANK.<br>B.Frame Relay is a BLANK switched technology that is a streamlined version of the older BLANK standard.<br>C.Frame Relay uses a best-effort technique, which means it simply BLANK packets when it detects errors, leaving any necessary error-correction (such as retransmission of data) up to the endpoints.<br>D.Frame Relay carries data between user BLANK devices and the BLANK devices at the edge of the WAN.<br>E.The connection through the Frame Relay network between two D T E's is called a virtual BLANK (VC).<br>F.BLANK virtual circuits are established dynamically by sending signaling messages to the network.<br>G.BLANK virtual circuits are preconfigured by the carrier and always operate in either DATA TRANSFER or IDLE mode.<br>H.Virtual circuits provide bi-directional communications and are uniquely identified by a BLANK, which has no significance beyond the single link.<br><br>Words:<br>price.<br>DCE.<br>flexibility.<br>BECN.<br>forwards. <br>Switched.<br>FECN.<br>packet.<br>ISDN.<br>constant.<br>X.25.<br>drops.<br>D T E.<br>circuit.<br>permanent.<br>DLCI.<br><br>Activity Two: In this activity, sequence the field labels in the proper order, from left to right, for a Frame Relay header address (two bytes). The C/R and E A fields are already inserted at the end of Byte One. The E A field is already inserted at the end of Byte Two.<br><br>Field Labels:<br>Address.<br>BECN.<br>Control.<br>D E.<br>DLCI.<br>FECN.<br><br>Activity Three: In this activity, match the name of the topology to each of the three diagrams as described below. Not all answers are used.<br><br>Diagram One Topology:<br>Consists of five routers, R1, R2, R3, R4, and R5.<br>R1 is connected to R2, R3, and R4.<br>R2 is connected to R1 and R3.<br>R3 is connected to R1 and R2.<br>R4 is connected to R1 and R5.<br><br>Diagram Two Topology:<br>Consists of four routers, R1, R2, R3, and R4.<br>R1 is connected to R2, R3, and R4.<br>R2 is connected to R1.<br>R3 is connected to R1.<br>R4 is connected to R1.<br><br>Diagram Three Topology:<br>Consists of four routers, R1, R2, R3, and R4.<br>R1 is connected to R2, R3, and R4.<br>R2 is connected to R1, R3, and R4.<br>R3 is connected to R1, R2, and R4.<br>R4 is connected to R1, R2, and R3.<br><br>Topology Names:<br>Bus.<br>Hub and Spoke.<br>Full Mesh.<br>Partial Mesh.<br>Ring.<br>Star.<br><br>Activity Four: In this activity, select the appropriate word or phrase to fill in the BLANK or BLANKs and complete the sentence. Not all answers are used, and some answers may be used more than once.<br><br>Sentences:<br>A.Dynamic address mapping relies on the Frame Relay BLANK to resolve a next hop network protocol address to a local DLCI value.<br>B.To configure static address mapping, use the BLANK command in interface configuration mode.<br>C.The BLANK extensions to the Frame Relay protocol provide additional capabilities for complex internetworking environments.<br>D.The LMI types include cisco, BLANK, and BLANK.<br>E.BLANK combined with BLANK messages allow a router to associate Network Layer and Data Link Layer addresses.<br><br>Words:<br>ISDN.<br>q 933 a.<br>Inverse ARP.<br>DLCI.<br>ansi.<br>LMI status messages.<br>Local Management Interface.<br>frame-relay map.<br>frame-relay lmi.<br>IETF.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
