<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 13:12:16">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[7.3.9 - Verifying and Troubleshooting RIP n g]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts Cisco I O S commands for verifying and troubleshooting RIP n g for IPv6.<br><br>Verifying:<br>Command: show i pv6 interface<br>Purpose: Displays the status of interfaces configured for IPv6.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 interface brief<br>Purpose: Displays a summarized status of interfaces configured for IPv6.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 neighbors<br>Purpose: Displays IPv6 neighbor discovery cache information.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 protocols<br>Purpose: Displays the parameters and current state of the active IPv6 routing protocol processes.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 rip<br>Purpose: Displays information about current IPv6 RIP processes.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 route<br>Purpose: Displays the current IPv6 routing table.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 route summary<br>Purpose: Displays a summarized form of the current IPv6 routing table.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 routers<br>Purpose: Displays IPv6 router advertisement information received from other routers.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 static<br>Purpose: Displays only static IPv6 routes installed in the routing table.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 static 2001:db8:5555:0/16<br>Purpose: Displays only static route information about the specific address given.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 static interface serial0/0<br>Purpose: Displays only static route information with the specified interface as the outgoing interface.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 static detail<br>Purpose: Displays a more detailed entry for IPv6 static routes.<br><br>Command: show i pv6 traffic<br>Purpose: Displays statistics about IPv6 traffic.<br><br>Troubleshooting: <br><br>Command: clear i pv6 rip<br>Purpose: Deletes routes from the IPv6 RIP routing table and, if installed, routes in the IPv6 routing table.<br><br>Command: clear i pv6 route *<br>Purpose: Deletes all routes from the IPv6 routing table.<br>NOTE: Clearing all routes from the routing table causes high CPU use rates as the routing table is rebuilt.<br><br>Command: clear i pv6 route 2001:db8:c18:3::/64<br>Purpose: Clears this specific route from the IPv6 routing table.<br><br>Command: clear i pv6 traffic<br>Purpose: Resets IPv6 traffic counters.<br><br>Command: debug i pv6 packet<br>Purpose: Displays debug messages for IPv6 packets.<br><br>Command: debug i pv6 rip<br>Purpose: Displays debug messages for IPv6 RIP routing transactions.<br><br>Command: debug i pv6 routing<br>Purpose: Displays debug messages for IPv6 routing table updates and route cache updates.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
