<transcript lastedited="11.17.08 08:11:18">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[2.7.1 - Chapter Quiz]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[1.	Place the P P P establishment steps in the correct order.<br>Step description:<br>Test link quality (optional).<br>Negotiate Layer 3 protocol options.<br>Send link-establishment frames to negotiate options like MTU size, compression, and authentication.<br>Send configuration-acknowledgement frames.<br>NCP reaches Open state.<br><br>Step number:<br>Step One.<br>Step Two.<br>Step Three.<br>Step Four.<br>Step Five.<br><br>2.	Which output from the show interfaces s0/0/0 command indicates that the far end of a point-to-point link has a different encapsulation set than the local router?<br>A.	serial 0/0/0 is down, line protocol is down.<br>B.	serial 0/0/0 is up, line protocol is down.<br>C.	serial 0/0/0 is up, line protocol is up (looped).<br>D.	serial 0/0/0 is up, line protocol is down (disabled).<br>E.	serial 0/0/0 is administratively down, line protocol is down.<br><br>3.	What is the default encapsulation for serial interfaces on a Cisco router?<br>A.	HDLC<br>B.	P P P<br>C.	Frame Relay<br>D.	X.25<br><br>4.	What is the function of the protocol field in a P P P frame?<br>A.	It identifies the Application Layer protocol that processes the frame.<br>B.	It identifies the Transport Layer protocol that processes the frame.<br>C.	It identifies the Data Link Layer protocol encapsulated in the data field of the frame.<br>D.	It identifies the Network Layer protocol encapsulated in the data field of the frame.<br><br>5.	Match the term to the associated description. Not all terms are used.<br>Terms: <br>Stacker/predictor.<br>Magic number.<br>Multilink.<br>CHAP/PAP.<br>Call in.<br><br>Descriptions:<br>error control.<br>authentication protocol.<br>allows load balancing.<br>compression protocol.<br><br>6.	Which three statements describe the function of time-division multiplexing. (Choose three.)<br>A.	Multiple data streams share one common channel.<br>B.	Bit interleaving controls the timing mechanism that places data on the channel.<br>C.	Time slots are utilized on a first-come, first-served basis.<br>D.	Statistical time-division multiplexing (STDM) was developed to overcome the inefficiency caused by time slots still being allocated, even when the channel has no data to transmit.<br>E.	Sources of data alternate during transmission and are reconstructed at the receiving end.<br>F.	Priority can be dedicated to one data source.<br><br>7.	What describes the serial connection between two routers using the HDLC protocol?<br>A.	synchronous or asynchronous bit-oriented transmissions using a universal frame format.<br>B.	synchronous bit-oriented transmissions using a frame format that allows flow control and error detection.<br>C.	asynchronous bit-oriented transmissions using a frame format derived from the Synchronous Data Link Control (SDLC) protocol.<br>D.	asynchronous bit-oriented transmissions using a V.35 D T E/DCE interface.<br><br>8.	If an authentication protocol is configured for P P P operation, when is the client or user workstation authenticated?<br>A.	prior to link establishment.<br>B.	during the link establishment phase.<br>C.	before the Network Layer protocol configuration begins.<br>D.	after the Network Layer protocol configuration has ended.<br><br>9.	Why are Network Control Protocols used in P P P?<br>A.	to establish and terminate data links.<br>B.	to provide authentication capabilities to P P P.<br>C.	to manage network congestion and to allow quality testing of the link.<br>D.	to allow multiple Layer 3 protocols to operate over the same physical link.<br><br>10.	Which statement describes PAP?<br>A.	It sends encrypted passwords by default.<br>B.	It uses a two-way handshake to establish identity.<br>C.	It protects against repeated trial-and-error attacks.<br>D.	It requires the same username to be configured on every router.<br><br>11.	A technician testing functionality of a recently installed router is unable to ping the serial interface of a remote router. The technician executes the show interface serial 0/0 command on the local router and sees the following line in the router:<br><br>Serial 0/0 is down, line protocol is down<br><br>What are two possible causes for this command output? (Choose two.)<br>A.	clockrate command missing.<br>B.	carrier detect signal not sensed.<br>C.	keepalives not being sent.<br>D.	interface disabled due to high error rate.<br>E.	interface shutdown.<br>F.	cabling is faulty or incorrect.<br><br>12.	The network administrator is configuring Router 1 to connect to Router 2 using a three-way handshake authentication. Match the commands necessary to configure Router 1 to their descriptions. Not all commands are used.<br><br>Commands:<br>username Router 2 password cisco<br>username Router 1 password cisco<br>interface serial 0/1/0<br>encapsulation p p p<br>encapsulation hdlc<br>p p p authentication pap<br>p p p authentication chap<br><br>Descriptions:<br>configure the username and password.<br>enter interface configuration mode.<br>specify encapsulation type.<br>configure authentication.<br><br>13.	What is required to establish a connection between two routers using CHAP authentication?<br>A.	The hostnames of both routers must be the same.<br>B.	The usernames of both routers must be the same.<br>C.	The enable secret passwords configured on both routers must be the same.<br>D.	The password configured with the username of the router must be the same on both routers.<br>E.	The p p p chap sent-username command must be configured the same on both routers.<br><br>14.	Match each characteristic with the authentication protocol.<br>Characteristics:<br>two-way handshake.<br>three-way handshake.<br>open to trial-and-error attacks.<br>password sent in clear text.<br>periodic verification.<br>uses one-way hash function.<br><br>Protocols: <br>PAP.<br>CHAP.<br><br>15.	Match the descriptions to the appropriate protocol. Not all descriptions are used.<br>Descriptions:<br>negotiates link establishment parameters.<br>negotiates Layer 3 protocol parameters.<br>maintains / debugs the link.<br>can negotiate multiple Layer 3 protocols.<br>terminates link.<br>only negotiates IP and AppleTalk.<br>uses MD5 encryption.<br><br>Protocols:<br>LCP.<br>NCP.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
