<transcript lastedited="01.09.09 09:01:27">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[3.1.2  - Virtual Circuits]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts virtual circuits in a Frame Relay network. Information is provided on Data Link Connection Identifiers (DLCI's), local significance, and identifying VC's.<br><br>Virtual Circuits:<br>A group of switches is interconnected in a Frame Relay cloud. Switches A, B, C, and D are identified. Two routers are shown, each connected to a Frame Relay switch at the edge of the cloud. The router labeled DLCI 102 is connected to switch A, and the router labeled DLCI 201 is connected to switch D. A virtual circuit is set up from router DLCI 102 through switches A, B, C, and D to router DLCI 201.<br><br>As the animation progresses, a frame passes from router DLCI 102 through the Frame Relay virtual circuit to router DLCI 201.<br><br>Local Significance:<br>The diagram is the same as the one for virtual circuits except that two additional routers have been added, connecting to other Frame Relay edge switches. These are labeled DLCI 319 and DLCI 624.<br><br>DLCI values have local significance, which means that they are unique only to the physical channel on which they reside. Therefore, devices at opposite ends of a connection can use the same DLCI values to refer to different virtual circuits.<br><br>Identifying VCs:<br>The diagram is the same as the one for virtual circuits, except that switches A, B, C, and D have port number labels on each Frame Relay connection. A virtual circuit is set up from router DLCI 102 through switches A, B, C, and D to router DLCI 201.<br><br>As the animation progresses, a frame passes from router DLCI 102 through the various Frame Relay switch ports to router DLCI 201. A table shows the switch port numbers for each leg of the virtual circuit transmission path as follows:<br><br>The frame starts at the router with DLCI 102.<br><br>Leg / Switch: A<br>Incoming VC: 102<br>Incoming Port: 0<br>Outgoing VC: 432<br>Outgoing Port: 1<br><br>Leg / Switch: B<br>Incoming VC: 432<br>Incoming Port: 4<br>Outgoing VC: 119<br>Outgoing Port: 1<br><br>Leg / Switch: C<br>Incoming VC: 119<br>Incoming Port: 4<br>Outgoing VC: 579<br>Outgoing Port: 3<br><br>Leg / Switch: D<br>Incoming VC: 579<br>Incoming Port: 3<br>Outgoing VC: 201<br>Outgoing Port: 0<br><br>The frame ends at the router with DLCI 201.]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
