<transcript lastedited="12.03.08 11:12:48">
<title><content-text><![CDATA[6.2.3 - DSL]]></content-text></title>
<brief><content-text><![CDATA[The diagram depicts additional information on separating data from voice in A DSL connections. An A DSL topology is presented along with diagrams showing how microfilters and splitters are used to separate voice and data.<br><br>A DSL: <br>- A key feature of A DSL is coexistence with POTS.<br>- Transmission of voice and data signals is performed on the same wire pair.<br>- Data circuits are offloaded from the voice switch.<br><br>A home location labeled Customer Premises contains an A DSL modem (CPE), a PC, an analog phone, and a microfilter. The PC connects to the A DSL modem and then to the phone line. The phone line connects to the network interface device (N ID) on the outside of the home. <br><br>The telephone connects to a microfilter that is between the phone and the phone line within the home. The phone line carries both POTS and A DSL to the telephone company C O. At the C O, a POTS splitter separates analog voice and directs it to a Class 5 PSTN switch. The splitter directs A DSL data to the D SLAM.<br><br>Microfilters: <br>The diagram shows a typical SOHO DSL layout using microfilters. An inline microfilter can be installed for each telephone or a wall-mounted microfilter can be used in place of regular telephone jacks. Rolling over the microfilters on the diagram shows photos of Cisco EZ-DSL inline and wall-mounted products.<br><br>Splitters: <br>A splitter is placed between the N ID and the inside telephone distribution system. One pair of wires goes directly to the DSL modem, and the other carries the voice signal to the telephones. Rolling over the splitter box on the diagram shows a typical wiring scheme, where a single pair of wires comes into the N ID from the telephone company and is split into two pairs. One pair goes to the DSL data jack, and one pair goes to the phone jacks.<br>]]></content-text></brief>
<full><content-text><![CDATA[FULL - NOT FOR PRODUCTION]]></content-text></full>
</transcript>
